<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoT App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_house_arryn">HouseArryn</string>

    <!-- Main Page Strings -->
    <string name="mp_great_houses_a_l">Great Houses A - L</string>
    <string name="mp_great_houses_m_t">Great Houses M - T</string>
    <string name="mp_organisations">Organisations</string>
    <string name="mp_religions">Religions</string>
    <string name="mp_seasons">Seasons</string>

    <!-- Great Houses A - L -->
    <string name="great_houses_a_l_arryn">Arryn</string>
    <string name="great_houses_a_l_baratheon">Baratheon</string>
    <string name="great_houses_a_l_bolton">Bolton</string>
    <string name="great_houses_a_l_frey">Frey</string>
    <string name="great_houses_a_l_greyjoy">Greyjoy</string>
    <string name="great_houses_a_l_lannister">Lannister</string>

    <!-- House Arryn -->
    <string name="title_house_arryn">House Arryn</string>
    <string name="call_house_arryn">&#8220;As High As Honor&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_arryn">House Arryn is one of the Great Houses of Westeros. It has
        ruled over the Vale of Arryn for millennia, originally as the Kings of Mountain and Vale
        and more recently as Lords Paramount of the Vale and Wardens of the East under the
        Targaryen kings and King Robert Baratheon. The nominal head of House Arryn is Robin Arryn,
        the Lord of the Eyrie, with his mother Lady Lysa acting as Lady Regent until he reaches the
        age of majority.</string>

    <!-- House Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_house_baratheon">House Baratheon</string>
    <string name="call_house_baratheon">&#8220;Ours is the Fury&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_baratheon">House Baratheon of Storm&#8217;s End was one of the Great Houses
        of Westeros, although also one of the youngest. It is the current royal house. \n\n
        House Baratheon&#8217;s sigil is a black stag on a gold background and their house motto is
        &#8221;Ours is the Fury&#8221;. When Robert ascended the Iron Throne, a gold crown was
        added to the stag, denoting their status as the royal house. \n\n The ancestral Baratheon
        stronghold is Storm&#8217;s End, but since becoming the royal house, they have also taken
        possession of the old Targaryen island fortress of Dragonstone, while the King rules
        from the city of King&#8217;s Landing, the capital of the Seven Kingdoms.</string>

    <!-- House Bolton -->
    <string name="title_house_bolton">House Bolton</string>
    <string name="call_house_bolton">&#8220;Our Blades Are Sharp&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_bolton">House Bolton of the Dreadfort is the ruling house of the
        North, having usurped their position from their former liege lords: House Stark. Their
        original lands are in the northeast of the formerly-owned Stark territories. Their
        stronghold is a castle called the Dreadfort and the head of the house is the Lord of
        the Dreadfort. \n\n House Bolton is infamous for its centuries-old practice of flaying
        their enemies alive, to the point that they use a flayed man as their House sigil.
        The Boltons supposedly gave up this practice after bending the knee to House Stark,
        and centuries later Lord Eddard Stark outlawed flaying in the North altogether,
        but the Boltons continue the practice.</string>

    <!-- House Frey -->
    <string name="title_house_frey">House Frey</string>
    <string name="call_house_frey">Those traitor&#8217;s don&#8217;t have a call.</string>
    <string name="story_house_frey">House Frey is the current Great House of the Riverlands,
        having gained their position for their treachery against their former liege lords,
        House Tully, who were stripped of all their titles for their rebellion against the
        Iron Throne. They are also now the Lords of Riverrun. Its current ruler is Lord Walder
        Frey. \n\n Their castle is known as the Twins, for its two identical keeps on either side
        of a river linked by a bridge, sometimes called the Stone Bridge. The Twins is one of the
        primary crossings over the Green Fork of the Trident River, and tolls from bridge
        crossings have made the Freys quite wealthy fairly quickly, elevating them from obscurity
        six centuries ago to being one of the most powerful noble Houses in the Riverlands -
        though they are looked down upon by older aristocratic families.</string>

    <!-- House Greyjoy -->
    <string name="title_house_greyjoy">House Greyjoy</string>
    <string name="call_house_greyjoy">&#8220;We Do Not Sow&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_greyjoy">House Greyjoy is one of the Great Houses of Westeros. Their
        lands are the Iron Islands off the west coast of the continent. They rule from their
        castle Pyke from the island of the same name. The Iron Islands are harsh and bleak and
        the Greyjoys have traditionally survived by raiding their neighbors. They have always had
        plans to conquer the mainland. The head of the house is the Lord Reaper of Pyke. \n\n
        House Greyjoy boasts descent from the Grey King, a legendary King of the Iron Islands
        said to have ruled for a thousand years and taken a mermaid as wife. Like the vast
        majority of ironborn, they worship the Drowned God.</string>

    <!-- House Lannister -->
    <string name="title_house_lannister">House Lannister</string>
    <string name="call_house_lannister">&#8220;Hear me roar!&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_lannister">House Lannister of Casterly Rock is one of the Great
        Houses of Westeros, one of its richest and most powerful families and oldest dynasties.
        The major characters Jaime, Cersei, and Tyrion and the recurring characters Tywin, Kevan,
        and Lancel are members of the house. Tywin is the head of House Lannister and Lord of
        Casterly Rock. \n\n Their lands are in the far west of the continent. Their seat is
        Casterly Rock, a massive rocky promontory overlooking the Sunset Sea which has had
        habitations and fortifications built into it over the millennia. They are the Lords
        Paramount of the Westerlands and Wardens of the West. House Lannister&#8217;s Heraldry consists
        of a golden lion on a crimson background, and their House words are &#8220;Hear me
        roar!&#8220;, which is rarely mentioned. Their unofficial motto, which is as well known
        as the official one, is &#8220;A Lannister always pays his debts&#8220; - which is used
        much more often and mostly in negative context, though it can also be used in the
        original, literal sense.</string>

    <!-- Great Houses M - T -->
    <string name="great_houses_m_t_martell">Martell</string>
    <string name="great_houses_m_t_stark">Stark</string>
    <string name="great_houses_m_t_targaryen">Targaryen</string>
    <string name="great_houses_m_t_tully">Tully</string>
    <string name="great_houses_m_t_tyrell">Tyrell</string>

    <!-- House Martell -->
    <string name="title_house_martell">House Martell</string>
    <string name="call_house_martell">&#8220;Unbowed, Unbent, Unbroken&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_martell">House Martell of Sunspear is one of the Great Houses of
        Westeros. It rules the peninsula of Dorne in the far south of the continent from their
        castle Sunspear. Though loyal to the Iron Throne, it has pursued a more isolated role
        in wider political events since Robert&#8217;s Rebellion.</string>

    <!-- House Stark -->
    <string name="title_house_stark">House Stark</string>
    <string name="call_house_stark">&#8220;Winter is Coming&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_stark">House Stark of Winterfell is an exiled Great House of
        Westeros, ruling over the vast region known as the North from their seat in Winterfell.
        It is by far one of the oldest lines of Westerosi nobility, claiming a line of descent
        stretching back over eight thousand years. The head of the house was the Lord of
        Winterfell. Before the Targaryen conquest, the leaders of House Stark ruled over
        the region as the Kings in the North. \n\n Their rule in the North seemingly ended after
        the events of the Red Wedding when House Frey and House Bolton betrayed them, and
        Roose Bolton personally killed King Robb Stark. Both the North and Winterfell have since
        been taken over by the Boltons but their hold has been jeopardized now that Sansa Stark
        has escaped their clutches after learning that her brothers Bran and Rickon Stark
        are still alive.</string>

    <!-- House Targaryen -->
    <string name="title_house_targaryen">House Targaryen</string>
    <string name="call_house_targaryen">&#8220;Fire and Blood&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_targaryen">House Targaryen is a former Great House of Westeros and
        was the ruling royal House of the Seven Kingdoms for three centuries, before it was deposed
        during Robert&#8217;s Rebellion and House Baratheon replaced it as the new royal House. The few
        surviving Targaryens fled into exile.</string>

    <!-- House Tully -->
    <string name="title_house_tully">House Tully</string>
    <string name="call_house_tully">&#8220;Family, Duty, Honor.&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_tully">House Tully is one of the Great Houses of Westeros. Their
        lands are to the west of the continent. Their seat is Riverrun, a castle at the confluence
        of the Red Fork of the Trident with the Tumblestone. They rule over the Riverlands from the
        castle and the head of the house is the Lord of Riverrun. \n\n House Tully rose to
        prominence during the Wars of Conquest. Lord Edmyn Tully rebelled against the King of the
        Isles and the Riverlands, Harren the Black, to support the invading House Targaryen.
        Edmyn&#8217;s fellow Riverlords followed his lead. When Aegon Targaryen established his rule
        from the Iron Throne he rewarded Edmyn, elevating the Tullys to Lords Paramount of the
        Riverlands. \n\n Its current head is Lord Edmure Tully. His sisters, Catelyn and Lysa,
        married Lords Eddard Stark and Jon Arryn during Robert&#8217;s Rebellion, forming a powerful
        alliance of major houses.</string>

    <!-- House Tyrell -->
    <string name="title_house_tyrell">House Tyrell</string>
    <string name="call_house_tyrell">&#8220;Growing Strong&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_house_tyrell">House Tyrell of Highgarden is one of the Great Houses of
        Westeros. It rules over the Reach, a vast, fertile, and heavily-populated region of
        southwestern Westeros, from their castle-seat, Highgarden. It is currently led by Lord
        Mace Tyrell, although his mother, the indomitable Olenna Tyrell, still wields considerable
        influence over the House&#8217;s affairs and is usually considered the true leader of the family.
        Mace&#8217;s son Loras is a noted tournament knight (and, secretly, the lover of Lord Renly
        Baratheon). Mace&#8217;s daughter Margaery married Renly when he crowned himself king, to cement
        the alliance between Renly and her father. Following Renly&#8217;s death, Margaery was then
        married to King Joffrey Baratheon before his assassination at his wedding feast. She is
        now married to the king, Tommen Baratheon.</string>

    <!-- Organisations -->
    <string name="organisations_brotherhood">Brotherhood without Banners</string>
    <string name="organisations_iron_bank">Iron Bank</string>
    <string name="organisations_kingsguard">Kingsguard</string>
    <string name="organisations_nightswatch">Night&#8217;s Watch</string>

    <!-- Brotherhood without Banners -->
    <string name="title_organisation_brotherhood">Brotherhood without Banners</string>
    <string name="story_organisation_brotherhood">The Brotherhood Without Banners is an outlaw
        group working against Lannister interests in the Riverlands at the time of the War of the
        Five Kings, though their goal is to protect the smallfolk from any force preying on them,
        regardless of which King or Lord they support. \n\nThe group was indirectly created by
        Eddard Stark, when he sent out a force of knights to restore peace and justice to the
        Riverlands, bolstered by several of his own household guards from House Stark. Trapped
        behind enemy lines, they became a guerrilla fighting group, and were joined by deserters
        from different armies in the war as well as commoners trying to defend their homes. The
        Brotherhood continues to fight to protect the commoners of the Riverlands in the name of
        King Robert and Lord Eddard. \n\n Following the Red Wedding, the Brotherhood Without
        Banners is one of the few surviving groups who still actively resist Lannister
        rule of the Seven Kingdoms.</string>

    <!-- Iron Bank -->
    <string name="title_organisation_iron_bank">Iron Bank</string>
    <string name="story_organisation_iron_bank">The Iron Bank of Braavos is a bank in the Free City
        of Braavos. It is arguably the most powerful financial institution in the Known World, with
        clients across Essos and Westeros, including the government of the King of the Andals and
        the First Men who rules over the Seven Kingdoms. \n\n Just as a common saying about House
        Lannister is &#8220;A Lannister always pays his debts&#8221;, there is also a common saying
        that the bank often reminds its clients who fail to repay their loans: &#8220;the Iron Bank
        will have its due&#8221;. \n\n The symbol of the Iron Bank depicts two golden triangles
        crossed in the manner of an hourglass, with two hands extending from left and right of the
        point where the triangles meet, their palms held upwards.</string>

    <!-- Kingsguard -->
    <string name="title_organisation_kingsguard">Kingsguard</string>
    <string name="story_organisation_kingsguard">The Kingsguard is an elite group of seven knights,
        supposedly the greatest and most skilled warriors in all of Westeros, who serve as the
        royal bodyguard of the King of the Andals and the First Men. Their duty is to protect the
        king and the royal family from harm at all times. The Kingsguard swear the most holy of
        vows to fulfill their sacred duty, and - in theory - are meant to be the living exemplars
        of the pinnacle of knightly virtues. Like the brothers of the Night&#8217;s Watch, members of
        the Kingsguard are sworn for life and are forbidden from owning land, taking a wife, or
        fathering children.</string>

    <!-- Night's Watch -->
    <string name="title_organisation_nights_watch">The Night&#8217;s Watch</string>
    <string name="story_organisation_nights_watch">The Night&#8217;s Watch is a military order which
        holds and guards the Wall, the immense ice structure which separates the northern border
        of the Seven Kingdoms from the lands beyond. The order was led by Lord Commander Jon Snow
        from the stronghold of Castle Black up until his death by mutineers. And before Jon was
        led by Lord Commander Jeor Mormont, who also was killed in a mutiny. The current Lord
        Commander is still to be decided. \n\n The Night&#8217;s Watch consists of three groups: the
        Rangers, who fight, defend the Wall and patrol the Haunted Forest; the Builders,
        who maintain the Wall and the castles; and the Stewards, who support and feed the
        members of the Watch.</string>

    <!-- Religions -->
    <string name="title_religions">Religions</string>
    <string name="story_religions">A multitude of different religions are worshiped by different
        cultures and peoples in the Known World, across the two continents of Westeros and
        Essos.</string>
    <string name="religions_essos">Essos</string>
    <string name="religions_westeros">Westeros</string>

    <!-- Religions of Essos -->
    <string name="title_religions_essos">Religions of Essos</string>
    <string name="religion_great_stallion">Great Stallion</string>
    <string name="religion_lord_light">The Lord of Light</string>
    <string name="religion_many_faced_god">The Many-Faced God of Death</string>

    <!-- Great Stallion -->
    <string name="title_religion_great_stallion">Great Stallion</string>
    <string name="story_religion_great_stallion">The Great Stallion is a horse god revered as the
        deity of the Dothraki religion, mirroring the importance of these creatures in Dothraki
        culture. The religious beliefs of the Dothraki are complex, as there is little division
        in Dothraki society between what in other cultures might be called &#8220;religion&#8221;
        and &#8220;custom&#8221;.</string>

    <!-- The Lord of Light -->
    <string name="title_religion_lord_light">The Lord of Light</string>
    <string name="story_religion_lord_light">R&#8217;hllor, alternatively known as the Lord of Light,
        and is a deity widely worshiped in the continent of Essos. The Lord of Light has been
        described as a &#8220;fire god&#8221; and its clergy &#8220;fire priests&#8221;, as worship
        of the Lord of Light centers around fire and light. \n\n He is also known as the Red God,
        the Heart of Fire, and the God of Flame and Shadow. \n\n The faith of the Lord of Light is
        the majority religion in several of the Free Cities, and extends to Asshai in the distant
        east. Worship of the Lord of Light is almost unheard of in Westeros.</string>

    <!-- The Many Faced God -->
    <string name="title_religion_many_faced_god">The Many Faced God of Death</string>
    <string name="story_religion_many_faced_god">The Many-Faced God (alternatively known as the God
        of Death) is a deity worshipped by the mysterious cult of assassins known as the Faceless
        Men, who are headquartered in the Free City of Braavos.</string>


    <!-- Religions of Westeros -->
    <string name="title_religions_westeros">Religions of Westeros</string>
    <string name="religion_old_gods">Old Gods</string>
    <string name="religion_faith_seven">Faith of the Seven</string>
    <string name="religion_drowned_god">Drowned God</string>

    <!-- Old Gods -->
    <string name="title_religion_old_gods">Old Gods</string>
    <string name="story_religion_old_gods">Innumerable and nameless spirits of each tree, rock,
        and stream worshipped by the Children of the Forest and later by the First Men. The
        original religion of the continent, it was later pushed back by the Faith of the Seven.
        In the present day, it is the majority religion only in the North and Beyond the Wall,
        though there still exist a scattered minority of followers in the south of the
        continent.</string>

    <!-- Faith of the Seven -->
    <string name="title_religion_faith_seven">Faith of the Seven</string>
    <string name="story_religion_faith_seven">Introduced to Westeros during the Andal Invasion six
        thousand years ago, it has for millennia been the majority religion on the continent. In
        terms of number of followers, geographic spread, and influence on politics, the Faith of
        the Seven is the overwhelmingly dominant religion in Westeros. It is based on the worship
        of &#8220;The Seven&#8221; or the &#8220;Seven-faced God&#8221;, a single deity with seven
        &#8220;aspects&#8221; or &#8220;faces&#8221;.</string>

    <!-- Drowned God -->
    <string name="title_religion_drowned_god">Drowned God</string>
    <string name="story_religion_drowned_god">The local religion of the people of the Iron
        Islands. Worshipers of the Drowned God value maritime skill, as well as prowess in combat
        and in piratical raids. It is the least followed of the three major religions in Westeros
        as well as the least widespread, being restricted to the lightly populated Iron Islands.
        Nonetheless, as there are so few major religions on the continent, it is still the third
        largest religion, and is certainly dominant within the Iron Islands themselves.</string>

    <!-- Seasons -->
    <string name="season_first">First Season</string>
    <string name="season_second">Second Season</string>
    <string name="season_third">Third Season</string>
    <string name="season_fourth">Fourth Season</string>
    <string name="season_fifth">Fifth Season</string>
    <string name="season_sixth">Sixth Season</string>

    <!-- First Season -->
    <string name="title_season_first">First Season</string>
    <string name="season_01_plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_01">01</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_02">02</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_03">03</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_04">04</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_05">05</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_06">06</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_07">07</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_08">08</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_09">09</string>
    <string name="season_01_episode_10">10</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Plot -->
    <string name="title_season_01_plot">Season 1 Plot</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_plot">Season 1 spans a period of several months on a world where
        the seasons last for years at a time. The action begins in the unified Seven Kingdoms of
        Westeros as the long summer ends and winter draws near. Lord Eddard Stark is asked by his
        old friend, King Robert Baratheon, to serve as the Hand of the King following the death of
        the previous incumbent, Eddard&#8217;s mentor Jon Arryn. Eddard is reluctant, but receives
        intelligence suggesting that Jon was murdered. Eddard accepts Robert&#8217;s offer, planning to
        use his position and authority to investigate the alleged murder. \n\nMeanwhile, on the
        eastern continent of Essos, the exiled children of House Targaryen, which Robert destroyed
        to claim the throne, are plotting to return to Westeros and unseat the &#8217;usurper&#8217;. To this
        end, Viserys Targaryen arranges the marriage of his sister Daenerys to Khal Drogo, the
        leader of 40,000 Dothraki warriors, in return for the use of his warriors in invading
        Westeros. For her part, Daenerys just wants to find a safe refuge far away from King
        Robert&#8217;s assassins and her brother&#8217;s scheming ambition. \n\n Finally, on the northern-most
        border of the Seven Kingdoms the sworn brothers of the Night&#8217;s Watch guard the Wall, a
        300-mile-long colossal fortification of ice which has stood for thousands of years. The
        Watch defends the Wall against the depredations of the lawless wildlings who live beyond,
        but rumor speaks of a new threat arising in the lands of perpetual winter.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 01 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_01">&#8220;Winter is Coming&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_01">Lord Eddard Stark, ruler of the North, is summoned to
        court by his old friend, King Robert Baratheon, to serve as the King&#8217;s Hand. Eddard
        reluctantly agrees after learning of a possible threat to the king&#8217;s life. Eddard&#8217;s
        bastard son Jon Snow must make a painful decision about his own future, while in the
        distant east Viserys Targaryen plots to reclaim his father&#8217;s throne, usurped by Robert,
        by selling his sister in marriage.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 02 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_02">&#8220;The Kingsroad&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_02">An incident on the Kingsroad threatens Eddard and
        Robert&#8217;s friendship. Jon and Tyrion travel to the Wall, where they discover that the
        reality of the Night&#8217;s Watch may not match the heroic image of it.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 03 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_03">&#8220;Lord Snow&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_03">Jon Snow attempts to find his place amongst the
        Night&#8217;s Watch. Eddard and his daughters arrive at King&#8217;s Landing.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 04 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_04">&#8220;Cripples, Bastards and Broken Things&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_04">Tyrion stops at Winterfell on his way home and gets
        a frosty reception from Robb Stark. Eddard&#8217;s investigation into the death of his
        predecessor gets underway.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 05 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_05">&#8220;The Wolf and the Lion&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_05">Catelyn&#8217;s actions on the road have repercussions
        for Eddard. Tyrion enjoys the dubious hospitality of the Eyrie.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 06 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_06">&#8220;A Golden Crown&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_06">Viserys is increasingly frustrated by the lack of
        progress towards gaining his crown.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 07 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_07">&#8220;You Win or You Die&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_07">Eddard&#8217;s investigations in King&#8217;s Landing reach a
        climax and a dark secret is revealed.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 08 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_08">&#8220;The Pointy End&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_08">Tyrion joins his father&#8217;s army with unexpected
        allies. Events in King&#8217;s Landing take a turn for the worse as Arya&#8217;s lessons are put to
        the test.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 09 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_09">&#8220;Baelor&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_09">Catelyn must negotiate with the irascible Lord
        Walder Frey.</string>

    <!-- Season 01 Episode 10 -->
    <string name="title_season_01_episode_10">&#8220;Fire and Blood&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_01_episode_10">Daenerys must realize her destiny. Jaime finds
        himself in an unfamiliar predicament.</string>

    <!-- Second Season -->
    <string name="title_season_second">Second Season</string>
    <string name="season_02_plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_01">01</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_02">02</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_03">03</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_04">04</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_05">05</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_06">06</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_07">07</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_08">08</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_09">09</string>
    <string name="season_02_episode_10">10</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Plot -->
    <string name="title_season_02_plot">Season 2 Plot</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_plot">Season 2 spans several months on a world where the seasons
        last for years at a time. The Seven Kingdoms are at war, with the King in the North, Robb
        Stark, fighting to win independence for his people and those of the Riverlands. Robb
        decides that he must win the allegiance of the fiercely independent ironborn to his cause,
        and sends his best friend Theon Greyjoy to treat with his father, who is hatching plans of
        his own. Meanwhile, Joffrey Baratheon holds the Iron Throne with the backing of the
        powerful House Lannister, but his uncle Renly has also claimed the throne with the support
        of House Tyrell, whose armies are much larger. As they struggle for the throne, Tyrion
        Lannister arrives in King&#8217;s Landing to take matters in hand, only to face opposition from
        his scheming sister, Cersei, now the Queen Regent. \n\n However, there is another faction
        entering the picture. Stannis Baratheon, Robert&#8217;s younger brother and Renly&#8217;s older brother,
        has also claimed the Iron Throne. A proven battle commander and veteran of several wars,
        Stannis is known to be utterly without mercy to his enemies and will do what is right even
        if it destroys him. Advising him is Melisandre, an enigmatic priestess from the east, who
        believes Stannis is meant for a greater destiny, and Ser Davos Seaworth, an honest and
        honorable man uneasy with the shifts in power at Stannis&#8217; court. \n\n Far to the east,
        Daenerys Targaryen has hatched the only three dragons in the world. Eventually they will
        grow into terrifying monsters capable of destroying cities at her command, but for now
        they are still hatchlings and vulnerable. With her khalasar gone, Daenerys and her small
        band of followers must find a way across a forbidding wasteland and find new allies to
        support her claim to the Iron Throne. \n\n In the distant north, the Night&#8217;s Watch has
        mounted an expedition beyond the Wall, searching for missing rangers and investigating
        rumors of wildlings gathering in the mountains. For Jon Snow this will be a rite of
        passage as he is asked to make difficult choices, for the realm and for himself.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 01 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_01">&#8220;The North Remembers&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_01">War grips the continent of Westeros. As Tyrion
        Lannister tries to take his strong-willed nephew in hand in King&#8217;s Landing, Stannis
        Baratheon launches his own campaign to take the Iron Throne with the help of a mysterious
        priestess. In the east, Daenerys must lead her retinue through a desolate wasteland whilst
        beyond the Wall the Night&#8217;s Watch seeks the aid of a wildling.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 02 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_02">&#8220;The Night Lands&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_02">Stannis uses Ser Davos to seek out new allies for
        his war with the Lannisters. On the road north, Arya confides in Gendry. Robb Stark sends
        Theon Greyjoy to win an alliance with his father and the fierce warriors of the Iron
        Islands. Cersei and Tyrion clash on how to rule in King&#8217;s Landing.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 03 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_03">&#8220;What is Dead May Never Die&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_03">Catelyn Stark treats with King Renly in the hope of
        winning an alliance. Tyrion undertakes a complex plan in King&#8217;s Landing to expose an enemy.
        At Winterfell, Bran&#8217;s dreams continue to trouble him.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 04 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_04">&#8220;Garden of Bones&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_04">Tyrion attempts to restrain Joffrey&#8217;s cruelty.
        Catelyn attempts to broke a peace between Stannis and Renly. Daenerys and her followers
        arrive at the great city of Qarth and hope to find refuge there. Arya and Gendry arrive
        at Harrenhal, a great castle now under Lannister occupation.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 05 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_05">&#8220;The Ghost of Harrenhal&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_05">Confusion rages in the Stormlands in the wake of a
        devastating reversal. Catelyn must flee with a new ally, whilst Littlefinger sees an
        opportunity in the chaos. Theon seeks to prove himself to his father in battle. Arya
        receives a promise from the enigmatic Jaqen H&#8217;ghar. The Night&#8217;s Watch arrives at the Fist
        of the First Men. Daenerys Targaryen receives a marriage proposal.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 06 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_06">&#8220;The Old Gods and the New&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_06">Arya has a surprise visitor. Dany vows to take what
        is hers. Joffrey meets his subjects. Qhorin gives Jon a chance to prove himself.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 07 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_07">&#8220;A Man Without Honor&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_07">Jaime meets a relative. Theon hunts. Dany receives
        an invitation.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 08 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_08">&#8220;The Prince of Winterfell&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_08">Theon holds the fort. Arya calls in her debt with
        Jaqen. Robb is betrayed. Stannis and Davos approach their destination.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 09 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_09">&#8220;Blackwater&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_09">A massive battle rages for control of King&#8217;s
        Landing and the Iron Throne.</string>

    <!-- Season 02 Episode 10 -->
    <string name="title_season_02_episode_10">&#8220;Valar Morghulis&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_02_episode_10">Tyrion awakens to a changed situation. King Joffrey
        doles out rewards to his subjects. As Theon stirs his men to action, Luwin offers some
        final advice. Brienne silences Jaime. Arya receives a gift from Jaqen. Dany goes to a
        strange place. Jon proves himself to Qhorin.</string>

    <!-- Third Season -->
    <string name="title_season_third">Third Season</string>
    <string name="season_03_plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_01">01</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_02">02</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_03">03</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_04">04</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_05">05</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_06">06</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_07">07</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_08">08</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_09">09</string>
    <string name="season_03_episode_10">10</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Plot -->
    <string name="title_season_03_plot">Season 3 Plot</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_plot">Season 3 spans several months on a world where the seasons
        can last for years at a time. Autumn has fallen across the world, with winter not far
        behind. The people should be preparing for years of snow and ice, but the Seven Kingdoms
        of Westeros instead remain gripped by civil war. Would-be king Renly Baratheon has been
        assassinated, altering the alliances in the war. The cruel boy-king Joffrey Baratheon has
        won a great victory by securing an alliance with House Tyrell, with his supporters
        defeating his uncle Stannis in an epic battle. Joffrey now commands the largest armies
        in the realm and his triumph appears inevitable. \n\n King Robb Stark remains in the field,
        however his homeland, the North, is partially under ironborn occupation. Robb needs to
        decide on a course of action to win an overall victory. He must also win back the
        allegiance of House Frey, whom he has offended by breaking his marriage pact with them.
        King Robb has won every battle he has fought, but as with old King Robert, the Starks will
        have to see if good soldiers make good kings. \n\n Stannis Baratheon may be defeated and
        most of his army destroyed or scattered, but he is not out of the fight yet. Having
        retreated to his headquarters on Dragonstone island with his handful of surviving soldiers,
        Stannis&#8217; status as the last legitimate heir to his older brother Robert still casts a
        shadow over Joffrey&#8217;s claim to the throne. With the priestess Melisandre at his side,
        Stannis can still influence the course of the war by striking where least expected. \n\n
        The lives of many others still hang in the balance. Bran Stark and his protectors must
        cross the frozen wastelands of the North to reach the Wall, while Arya must brave the
        war-torn Riverlands in search of her mother and brother. Brienne of Tarth also has the
        thankless task of escorting the captive Jaime Lannister home across hundreds of miles of
        battlefields and carnage. Theon Greyjoy must face the consequences of his actions at
        Winterfell. And in King&#8217;s Landing both Tyrion Lannister and Sansa Stark must brave the
        currents of a much more dangerous court in order to survive. \n\n On the eastern continent,
        Daenerys Targaryen has fled the political viper-pit of Qarth. Her dragons are growing and
        her fame is spreading, but to take the Iron Throne she will need supporters and an army.
        Both may be found in the corrupt cities of Slaver&#8217;s Bay... for a price. \n\n Beyond the
        Wall, the White Walkers are on the move, threatening both the Seven Kingdoms and the lands
        of the Free Folk. While the Night&#8217;s Watch faces the threat of the White Walkers in the
        field, Jon Snow must infiltrate the wildling army of Mance Rayder and discover the
        King-Beyond-the-Wall&#8217;s plans.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 01 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_01">&#8220;Valar Dohaeris&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_01">Jon is brought before Mance Rayder, the King Beyond
        the Wall, while the Night&#8217;s Watch survivors retreat south. In King&#8217;s Landing, Tyrion asks
        for his reward, Littlefinger offers Sansa a way out, and Cersei hosts a dinner for the
        royal family. Dany sails into Slaver&#8217;s Bay.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 02 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_02">&#8220;Dark Wings, Dark Words&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_02">Sansa Stark is introduced to Olenna Tyrell and is
        incautious when questioned about King Joffrey Baratheon. Shae asks Tyrion Lannister for
        help protecting Sansa. Jaime Lannister provokes Brienne into a duel but finds himself
        recaptured. Arya Stark crosses paths with the Brotherhood Without Banners and is
        recognized by their new prisoner Sandor Clegane. Ravens bring dark news to the King in the
        North at Harrenhal; his brothers are still missing and Hoster Tully has died. Jon Snow
        learns about wargs from the Free Folk. Bran Stark is surprised to meet new allies in the
        barren North.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 03 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_03">&#8220;Walk of Punishment&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_03">Tyrion gains new responsibilities. Jon is taken to
        the Fist of the First Men. Daenerys meets with the slavers. Jaime strikes a deal with
        his captors.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 04 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_04">&#8220;And Now His Watch is Ended&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_04">The Night&#8217;s Watch takes stock. Varys meets his better.
        Arya is taken to the commander of the Brotherhood. Daenerys makes an exchange.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 05 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_05">&#8220;Kissed by Fire&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_05">The Hound is judged by the gods. Jaime is judged.
        Jon proves himself. Robb is betrayed. Tyrion learns the cost of weddings.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 06 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_06">&#8220;The Climb&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_06">Tywin plans strategic unions for the Lannisters.
        Melisandre pays a visit to the Riverlands. Robb weighs a compromise to repair his alliance
        with House Frey. Roose Bolton decides what to do with Jaime Lannister. Jon, Ygritte and
        the Wildlings face a daunting climb.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 07 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_07">&#8220;The Bear and the Maiden Fair&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_07">Dany exchanges gifts with a slave lord outside of
        Yunkai. As Sansa frets about her prospects, Shae chafes at Tyrion&#8217;s new situation. Tywin
        counsels the king, and Melisandre reveals a secret to Gendry. Brienne faces a formidable
        foe in Harrenhal.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 08 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_08">&#8220;Second Sons&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_08">King&#8217;s Landing hosts a wedding, and Tyrion and Sansa
        spend the night together. Dany meets the Titan&#8217;s Bastard. Davos demands proof from
        Melisandre. Sam and Gilly meet an older gentleman.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 09 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_09">&#8220;The Rains of Castamere&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_09">Robb presents himself to Walder Frey, and Edmure
        meets his bride. Jon faces his harshest test yet. Bran discovers a new gift. Daario and
        Jorah debate how to take Yunkai. House Frey joins with House Tully.</string>

    <!-- Season 03 Episode 10 -->
    <string name="title_season_03_episode_10">&#8220;Mhysa&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_03_episode_10">Joffrey challenges Tywin. Bran tells a ghost story.
        In Dragonstone, mercy comes from strange quarters. Dany waits to see if she is a conqueror
        or a liberator.</string>

    <!-- Fourth Season -->
    <string name="title_season_fourth">Fourth Season</string>
    <string name="season_04_plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_01">01</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_02">02</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_03">03</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_04">04</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_05">05</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_06">06</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_07">07</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_08">08</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_09">09</string>
    <string name="season_04_episode_10">10</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Plot -->
    <string name="title_season_04_plot">Season 4 Plot</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_plot">The War of the Five Kings is drawing to a close, but new
        intrigues and plots are in motion, and the surviving factions must contend with enemies not
        only outside their ranks, but within. \n\n King in the North Robb Stark is dead, betrayed
        by his own bannermen the Boltons and Freys while he was a guest under the Freys&#8217; roof.
        Robb&#8217;s mother Catelyn and his wife Talisa, along with most of the Northern leadership were
        also killed at the massacre now known as the Red Wedding, along with the entire Northern
        army. \n\n Having already defeated Stannis Baratheon at the Battle of the Blackwater and
        secured southern Westeros, House Lannister stands triumphant. The crazed boy-king Joffrey
        Baratheon gloats, though the victory truly belongs to his grandfather, Lord Tywin Lannister,
        Hand of the King and the real power behind the Iron Throne. As reward for their betrayal,
        Tywin has granted the Boltons rule of the North, and the Freys with nominal rule of
        Riverrun, though the castle remains under the command of Brynden Tully. \n\n Though the
        mainland of Westeros is mostly under Lannister control, there are still two factions
        defying them: the Greyjoys and the Baratheons. Ironborn occupiers remaining in the North
        are being hunted down by Ramsay Snow, bastard son of Roose Bolton. Ramsay holds Theon
        Greyjoy hostage, horribly torturing him at whim, but Balon Greyjoy considers his son as
        good as dead. \n\n Stannis Baratheon, as the rightful heir to his older brother King Robert,
        still refuses to surrender, despite having only the remnants of an army. However, following
        the advice of Melisandre, he has focused his attention of the threat of the wildlings
        marching against the Wall. \n\n The Lannisters only managed to win on the battlefield with
        the key support of House Tyrell of the Reach, which they won through promising a
        marriage-alliance between King Joffrey and Margaery Tyrell, daughter of Lord Mace Tyrell.
        Queen Regent Cersei fears - correctly - that just as the Baratheons became dependent on the
        Lannisters after Robert&#8217;s Rebellion, the Lannisters are starting to become dependent on
        the Tyrells, who are already insinuating themselves into positions of power at King&#8217;s
        Landing. A royal wedding is to be held between Joffrey and Margaery, which will confirm
        the future of the realm. \n\n The only two kingdoms which have remained entirely aloof
        from the war so far are the Vale of Arryn and Dorne. While Lysa Arryn chose to remain
        neutral, former Master of Coin and new Lord of Harrenhal Petyr Baelish has been sent by
        Lord Tywin to woo her with a marriage proposal, now that he&#8217;s a high lord and a suitable
        match for the Lady Regent of the Vale. Nevertheless only Littlefinger knows what
        Littlefinger is plotting. \n\n For their own part, House Martell of Dorne has loathed the
        Lannisters ever since the Sack of King&#8217;s Landing, when Ser Gregor Clegane raped and killed
        Elia Martell - sister of Doran Martell, the ruling Prince of Dorne - and Lord Tywin did
        nothing to punish him. During the War of the Five Kings Tyrion Lannister prevented Dorne
        from declaring for any of House Lannister&#8217;s enemies by sending Princess Myrcella to
        Sunspear as part of her betrothal to Prince Trystane Martell, and in return, the Martells
        were promised a seat on the Small Council. To the consternation of the Lannisters, a large
        Dornish embassy arrives in King&#8217;s Landing to claim their due - but instead of the elderly
        Prince Doran, his brash younger brother Prince Oberyn comes to claim the council seat.
        Oberyn loves the ladies, he loves the boys, but most of all he loved his sister Elia, and
        the Lannisters aren&#8217;t the only ones who pay their debts. \n\n Meanwhile, across the Narrow
        Sea in Slaver&#8217;s Bay, perhaps the greatest threat to Lannister rule is rapidly growing in
        strength. Daenerys Targaryen now commands not just three live dragons - who are starting to
        grow large enough to serve as decisive weapons of war - but also an army of eight thousand
        Unsullied warrior-eunuchs. For now, Queen Daenerys is carving a path through Slaver&#8217;s Bay
        - not of conquest but of liberation. As functionally once a slave herself, Daenerys is
        determined to free the downtrodden slaves of the region. First Astapor and then Yunkai fell
        before Daenerys&#8217;s forces, and hundreds of thousands of freed slaves now flock to her banner.
        Yet Daenerys must now face the last and greatest of the slaver-cities, Meereen - and unlike
        her previous victories, they have had time to prepare for her arrival. \n\n Far to the
        north, beyond the politics and meaningless feuds of the south, the Wall and the dwindling
        Night&#8217;s Watch are all that stand between the Seven Kingdoms and the horrors beyond. The
        White Walkers have emerged in force, leading their armies of wights. The wildlings have
        rallied behind King-Beyond-the-Wall Mance Rayder in an attempt to flee south, knowing that
        as the White Walkers advance, anyone who remain in the lands beyond the Wall will die and
        become part of the undead host. Mance&#8217;s wildling army now numbers in the tens of thousands,
        and is determined to force its way through the Wall to reach the safety of the south. All
        that stands between the Seven Kingdoms and this barbarian invasion is the Night&#8217;s Watch,
        whose numbers and leadership were recently devastated with the deaths of a third of their
        number and that of Lord Commander Jeor Mormont. Jon Snow and Samwell Tarly do what they can
        to prepare Castle Black for the massive wildling attack. \n\n Not only are the Night&#8217;s
        Watch outnumbered and their remaining leadership fractured, but advanced raiding bands of
        wildlings have infiltrated behind the Wall by climbing over it, preparing to attack the
        weakly defended southern side of Castle Black. These warbands are led by Tormund and the
        fearsome Styr, Magnar of Thenn - as well as Jon Snow&#8217;s ex-lover Ygritte, whom he betrayed
        when he revealed his true loyalty and returned to the Night&#8217;s Watch. \n\n In the Seven
        Kingdoms, while House Stark stands on the verge of extinction - and is believed to be just
        that by the realm at large - four &#8220;lone wolves&#8221; fight to survive: Sansa Stark
        remains a hostage of the Iron Throne and a forced marriage to Tyrion Lannister, Rickon
        Stark seeks the safety of Last Hearth and the fiercely loyal House Umber, Bran Stark and
        his companions Hodor, Jojen and Meera Reed have crossed the Wall chasing a vision, and Arya
        Stark, having lost everything and forced to rely on the protection of a man she hates,
        clings to survival and her thirst for vengeance.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 01 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_01">&#8220;Two Swords&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_01">Tyrion welcomes a guest to King&#8217;s Landing. At Castle
        Black, Jon Snow finds himself unwelcome. Dany is pointed to Meereen, the mother of all
        slave cities. Arya runs into an old friend.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 02 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_02">&#8220;The Lion and the Rose&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_02">A who&#8217;s who of honored guests turns out for Joffrey
        and Margaery&#8217;s wedding in King&#8217;s Landing. Meanwhile, Bronn gives a lesson to an unlikely
        pupil. Bran&#8217;s vision helps map out his journey. Stannis loses patience with Davos. Ramsay
        takes a perverse delight in his new pet.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 03 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_03">&#8220;Breaker of Chains&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_03">In the frenzied aftermath of the royal wedding,
        Tyrion gets a visit from a loyal subject. Meanwhile, Tywin offers to work for the common
        good with a presumed enemy. Sam takes stock of the personnel at Castle Black. The Hound
        gives another life lesson to Arya. Daenerys makes a decision outside the walls of
        Meereen.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 04 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_04">&#8220;Oathkeeper&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_04">Dany balances justice and mercy. Jaime tasks Brienne
        with his honor. Jon secures volunteers while Bran, Jojen, Meera and Hodor stumble on
        shelter.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 05 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_05">&#8220;First of His Name&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_05">Cersei and Tywin plot the Crowns next move. Dany
        discusses future plans. Jon embarks on a new mission.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 06 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_06">&#8220;The Laws of Gods and Men&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_06">Stannis and Davos set sail with a new strategy. Dany
        meets with supplicants. Tyrion faces down his father in the throne room.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 07 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_07">&#8220;Mockingbird&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_07">Tyrion enlists an unlikely ally. Daario entreats
        Dany to allow him to do what he does best. Jons warnings about the Walls vulnerability
        fall on deaf ears. Brienne follows a new lead on the road with Pod.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 08 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_08">&#8220;The Mountain and the Viper&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_08">Unexpected visitors arrive in Mole&#8217;s Town.
        Littlefinger&#8217;s motives are questioned. Ramsay tries to prove himself to his father.
        Tyrion&#8217;s fate is decided.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 09 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_09">&#8220;The Watchers on the Wall&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_09">Jon Snow and the Night&#8217;s Watch face a big
        challenge.</string>

    <!-- Season 04 Episode 10 -->
    <string name="title_season_04_episode_10">&#8220;The Children&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_04_episode_10">Circumstances change after an unexpected arrival
        from north of the Wall. Dany must face harsh realities. Bran learns more about his destiny.
        Tyrion sees the truth about his situation.</string>

    <!-- Fifth Season -->
    <string name="title_season_fifth">Fifth Season</string>
    <string name="season_05_plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_01">01</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_02">02</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_03">03</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_04">04</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_05">05</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_06">06</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_07">07</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_08">08</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_09">09</string>
    <string name="season_05_episode_10">10</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Plot -->
    <string name="title_season_05_plot">Season 5 Plot</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_plot">
        The War of the Five Kings, once thought to be drawing to a close, is instead entering a new
        and more chaotic phase. Westeros is on the brink of collapse, and many are seizing what
        they can while the realm implodes, like a corpse making a feast for crows. \n\n Tywin
        Lannister is dead, shot on the privy by his long-abused dwarf son Tyrion. The crazed
        boy-king Joffrey Baratheon, Tywin&#8217;s grandson, is also dead after being poisoned at his own
        wedding, and succeeded by his younger and more pliable brother, Tommen. Queen Cersei
        Lannister succeeds her father as the head of House Lannister, and once again takes over
        as Queen Regent, as Tommen has yet to come of age. Cersei has been blocked by several
        powerful men over the years, including her husband King Robert Baratheon and his friend
        Eddard Stark, but due to her betrayals they are both dead. Now with even Tywin and Joffrey
        dead, and Tyrion fleeing the realm, there are no more checks on Cersei&#8217;s power, and she is
        essentially the Ruling Queen of the Seven Kingdoms in all but name. However, Cersei is
        neither a master strategist nor a skilled diplomat (unlike her father and brother) and she
        faces mounting crises that would have strained even their abilities. \n\n House Lannister
        and its allies have managed to crush House Stark, but in many ways it was a pyrrhic victory.
        The Iron Throne was already in massive debt to foreign banks before the war even began,
        and the Lannisters&#8217; immense wartime spending increased the crown&#8217;s debts to crippling
        levels. The Lannisters must now desperately attempt to placate the Iron Bank of Braavos,
        by far the largest of the foreign banks, and the one which the crown owes most of its huge
        debts to. \n\n The game of thrones is, unfortunately, not a simple game of cyvasse in
        which the pieces can be quickly reassembled: vast swathes of Westeros have been devastated
        by civil war, and it may take a full generation for them to rebuild. The Riverlands, where
        most of the war was fought, have been reduced to a burned out husk. Nominally the
        Lannisters and their House Frey allies control the Riverlands, but it has been reduced to
        a lawless and corpse-filled devastation, hardly controlled by anyone. Winter is fast
        approaching, but instead of stockpiling harvests the past few years, the great lords have
        been busy destroying one of the main breadbasket regions of the Seven Kingdoms. Combined
        with the realm&#8217;s massive debts to foreign banks, starvation level conditions are starting
        to set in for the smallfolk across the realm. Outraged by the willful indifference of their
        rulers to their well-being for so long, commoners are starting to fall back onto old
        cultural touchstones, channeling their frustration into religious fanaticism. A popular
        disgust movement spreads across Westeros, and makes its way to the capital. \n\n Adding to
        these woes is the increasing rivalry between the Lannisters and their Tyrell allies,
        specifically between Cersei and Margaery Tyrell. The Lannisters only managed to win on the
        battlefield with the armies and food resources won by their alliance with the House Tyrell
        of the Reach. Now that Tywin is dead, and Margaery is soon to be King Tommen&#8217;s queen, the
        Tyrells are no longer pretending to be polite to the Lannisters, but openly demanding
        greater concessions and key positions of power. With half of the Lannister armies
        slaughtered by Robb Stark during the war, their financial resources depleted, and the
        Tyrells controlling the only major breadbasket region untouched by the war, the Lannisters
        are having to face the reality that the Tyrells hold numerous advantages over them. Just
        as Robert Baratheon became king only to become dependent on the support of the Lannisters,
        the Lannisters have now become dependent on the Tyrells. \n\n Without the political acumen
        of Tywin or Tyrion, Queen Regent Cersei struggles to address these major challenges. Adding
        even further to her woes is that the king&#8217;s Small Council has been gutted, with Hand of the
        King Tywin dead, Master of Coin Petyr Baelish leaving for the Eyrie, and both Tyrion and
        Master of Whisperers Varys fleeing the capital city. Of the original Small Council when the
        Lannisters first seized power, only Grand Maester Pycelle remains. \n\n Besides the Reach,
        only the regions which have remained neutral so far still have all of their armies and
        resources intact: the Vale, ruled by House Arryn, and Dorne, ruled by House Martell. With
        nearly all the other Great Houses defeated or half-exhausted, the fresh armies of the Vale
        and Dorne can drastically alter the political playing field, depending on which side they
        choose to join. \n\n The ultimate result of the war was to exhaust the Starks, Lannisters,
        and other Great Houses of the Seven Kingdoms - exactly as Petyr &#8220;Littlefinger&#8221; Baelish had
        planned. The secret architect of the conflict, it was Littlefinger who was responsible for
        poisoning Robert&#8217;s Hand, Jon Arryn, by conspiring with his own wife Lysa Arryn.
        Littlefinger then engineered the betrayal of Eddard Stark, only to later assist Olenna
        Tyrell in assassinating King Joffrey at his own wedding. Baelish has now murdered Lysa,
        mere days after wedding her, and seized power over the Vale as regent for her young son.
        For the moment, Baelish remains in the Vale, consolidating his new hold over the Vale
        lords through his stepson Robin and his position as Lord Protector of the Vale. Alongside
        Baelish is the black-haired &#8220;Alayne&#8221;, his ward and &#8220;niece&#8221; - secretly, Sansa Stark, who
        fell into Littlefinger&#8217;s custody after he helped her escape her long imprisonment at
        Joffrey&#8217;s royal court. \n\n In the deserts of the deep south of Westeros, the people of
        Dorne demand vengeance for the death of Prince Oberyn, who died in a trial by combat at the
        hands of Ser Gregor Clegane. Leading the call to enter the war against the Lannisters are
        Oberyn&#8217;s paramour, Ellaria Sand, and the eldest of his eight daughters: Obara, Nymeria,
        and Tyene. But Doran Martell, the Prince of Dorne and Oberyn&#8217;s older brother, continues
        to urge restraint. Further complicating the matter is that early in the war, the Lannisters
        bribed the Martells into staying neutral by offering a marriage-alliance, sending Cersei&#8217;s
        daughter Myrcella to Dorne to betroth her to Doran&#8217;s son Trystane. Myrcella is still a ward
        living in Dorne&#8217;s capital, Sunspear. \n\ The most dire situation in Westeros, however, is
        in the North and at the Wall. The massive assault against Castle Black by the wildling army
        of Mance Rayder was defeated at the last moment by the surprise arrival of Stannis
        Baratheon and his remaining forces. Stannis withdrew from his island stronghold Dragonstone
        to reach the Wall by sea, to defend the realm of which he feels he is the only rightful
        king. With his home territories in the Stormlands overrun, Stannis needs to win the
        allegiance of Robb Stark&#8217;s defeated bannermen, to rally the North again as a springboard
        against Lannister rule, as well as the support of Jon Snow, who therefore must walk a
        political tightrope between Stannis and his vows, since the Night&#8217;s Watch is sworn to
        strict political neutrality. Though the battle against the wildlings is all but over, the
        Night&#8217;s Watch is in its own dire conditions. With almost all of the Watch&#8217;s top officers
        either killed or missing, among them Lord Commander Jeor Mormont and First Ranger Benjen
        Stark, the organization has been left leaderless during this time of crisis, and therefore
        will have to navigate a contentious election for a new Lord Commander. All the while, the
        White Walkers and their ever-growing army of the dead are bearing down on the Wall itself,
        intent on spilling over it to destroy the lands of men beyond, who remain ignorant of the
        long-forgotten but all-too-real danger. \n\n The main armies of the Northern Houses,
        however, were slaughtered in the south at the Red Wedding, and the large main army of
        House Bolton has just returned to the North following the recapture of Moat Cailin. The
        Boltons switched to the Lannister side during the betrayal at the Red Wedding, during which
        their leader Lord Roose Bolton personally killed Robb Stark, and they have been installed
        as the new rulers of the North in the name of King Tommen and the Lannisters. With the
        other Northern Houses defeated and weakened, the Lannister-backed Bolton army can now
        suppress any feeble opposition to their rule. Meanwhile, Roose&#8217;s psychopathic bastard son
        Ramsay Snow - now legitimized as Ramsay Bolton - is the new Lord of Winterfell under his
        father, reoccupying the castle which he personally burned out previously. With the Boltons
        in power, Ramsay is now free to commit numerous atrocities throughout the North, such as
        flaying men alive and hunting and killing young women for sport. \n\n However, the struggle
        for the North is not yet over. Various areas of the North&#8217;s western coast are still held by
        ironborn invaders under Balon Greyjoy, who chose to crown himself as King of the Iron
        Islands and attack the North during Robb Stark&#8217;s march south rather than ally with him
        against the Lannisters. Balon&#8217;s son and heir, Theon, who himself was a ward of Lord Eddard
        Stark and one of Robb&#8217;s closest advisors, turned on the Starks and led the assault himself
        but was betrayed by his own men and is now a prisoner of the Boltons, having been brutally
        flayed, tortured, and psychologically broken by Ramsay himself, who has reduced Theon to
        his personal slave, &#8220;Reek&#8221;. \n\n East of Westeros, after murdering his own father, Tyrion
        Lannister has fled across the Narrow Sea to the Free Cities, his future intentions unknown
        even to himself. Accompanied by Varys, he arrives in the east, unaware that the erstwhile
        Master of Whisperers might yet have secrets to reveal. Further north, meanwhile,
        representatives from the Iron Throne travel to the Free City of Braavos to assuage the Iron
        Bank&#8217;s frustrations about all of the money the Lannisters owe. Unbeknownst to all, Arya
        Stark has also fled to Braavos, due to a favor she was owed for saving the life of one of
        the mysterious guild of assassins in Braavos known as the Faceless Men. \n\n Further east
        in Slaver&#8217;s Bay, Daenerys Targaryen&#8217;s hold over Meereen has become very precarious, as
        ruling the city is becoming much more difficult than conquering it was. Sectarian violence
        is rampant between the former slaves and former slave-masters, revenge attacks are on the
        rise, and the resurgent slavers at Yunkai are rallying all those who oppose her. Daenerys&#8217;s
        three dragons, now growing to dangerous size, have become uncontrollable and she can no
        longer rely upon them to defeat her enemies on the battlefield. Drogon burned a child to
        death while he was hunting and fled the city, forcing Daenerys to chain up the remaining
        two dragons in the caverns underneath the city. In addition, Daenerys is still distraught
        over the recent revelations concerning her once-trusted advisor Jorah Mormont, whom she
        exiled from the city as punishment. Her remaining advisors Ser Barristan Selmy, Missandei,
        and the sellsword Daario Naharis attempt to help hold her reign together. \n\n But
        unbeknownst to Daenerys, word has finally spread to Westeros that the last living Targaryen
        heir has hatched three live dragons. No longer a mere curiosity halfway across the world,
        several different factions in Westeros are now pondering how Daenerys and her dragons will
        factor into the already confusing and multi-sided civil war still tearing the Seven Kingdoms
        apart. Envoys are beginning to head east to court Daenerys&#8217;s allegiance: but those who try
        to dance with dragons run the risk of being burned.
    </string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 01 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_01">&#8220;The Wars to Come&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_01">Cersei and Jaime adjust to a world without Tywin.
        Varys reveals a conspiracy to Tyrion. Dany faces a new threat to her rule. Jon is caught
        in between two kings.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 02 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_02">&#8220;The House of Black and White&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_02">Arya arrives in Braavos. Pod and Brienne run into
        trouble on the road. Cersei fears for her daughters safety in Dorne as Ellaria Sand seeks
        revenge for Oberyns death. Stannis tempts Jon. An adviser tempts Dany.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 03 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_03">&#8220;High Sparrow&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_03">In Braavos, Arya sees the Many-Faced God. In Kings
        Landing, Queen Margaery enjoys her new husband. Tyrion and Varys walk the Long Bridge of
        Volantis.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 04 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_04">&#8220;Sons of the Harpy&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_04">The Faith Militant grow increasingly aggressive.
        Jaime and Bronn head south. Ellaria and the Sand Snakes vow vengeance.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 05 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_05">&#8220;Kill the Boy&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_05">Dany makes a difficult decision in Meereen. Jon
        recruits the help of an unexpected ally. Brienne searches for Sansa. Theon remains under
        Ramsays control.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 06 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_06">&#8220;Unbowed, Unbent, Unbroken&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_06">Arya trains. Jorah and Tyrion run into slavers.
        Trystane and Myrcella make plans. Jaime and Bronn reach their destination. The Sand
        Snakes attack.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 07 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_07">&#8220;The Gift&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_07">Jon prepares for conflict. Sansa tries to talk to
        Theon. Brienne waits for a sign. Stannis remains stubborn. Jaime attempts to reconnect
        with family.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 08 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_08">&#8220;Hardhome&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_08">Arya makes progress in her training. Sansa confronts
        an old friend. Cersei struggles. Jon travels.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 09 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_09">&#8220;The Dance of Dragons&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_09">Stannis confronts a troubling decision. Jon returns
        to the Wall. Mace visits the Iron Bank. Arya encounters someone from her past. Daenerys
        relunctantly oversees a traditional celebration of athleticism.</string>

    <!-- Season 05 Episode 10 -->
    <string name="title_season_05_episode_10">&#8220;Mother&#8217;s Mercy&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_05_episode_10">Stannis marches. Dany is surrounded by strangers.
        Cersei seeks forgiveness. Jon is challenged.</string>

    <!-- Sixth Season -->
    <string name="title_season_sixth">Sixth Season</string>
    <string name="season_06_plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_01">01</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_02">02</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_03">03</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_04">04</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_05">05</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_06">06</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_07">07</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_08">08</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_09">09</string>
    <string name="season_06_episode_10">10</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 01 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_01">&#8220;The Red Woman&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_01">April 24, 2016 \n\n Jon Snow is dead. Daenerys meets a
        strong man. Cersei sees her daughter again.</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 02 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_02">&#8220;Home&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_02">May 1, 2016 \n\n Bran trains with the Three-Eye Raven.
        In King&#8217;s Landing, Jaime advises Tommen. Tyrion demands good news, but has to make his own.
        At Castle Black, the Night&#8217;s Watch stands behind Thorne. Ramsay Bolton proposes a plan, and
        Balon Greyjoy entertains other proposals.</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 03 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_03">&#8220;Oathbreaker&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_03">May 8, 2016 \n\n Daenerys meets her future. Bran meets
        the past. Tommen confronts the High Sparrow. Arya trains to be No One. Varys finds the
        answer. Ramsay gets a gift.</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 04 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_04">&#8220;Book of the Stranger&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_04">May 15, 2016</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 05 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_05">&#8220;Door&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_05">May 22, 2016</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 06 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_06">&#8220;Episode 6&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_06">May 29, 2016</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 07 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_07">&#8220;Episode 7&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_07">June 5, 2016</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 08 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_08">&#8220;Episode 8&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_08">June 12, 2016</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 09 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_09">&#8220;Episode 9&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_09">June 19, 2016</string>

    <!-- Season 06 Episode 10 -->
    <string name="title_season_06_episode_10">&#8220;Episode 10&#8221;</string>
    <string name="story_season_06_episode_10">June 26, 2016</string>

    <!-- Character Stark Eddard -->
    <string name="title_character_stark_eddard">Eddard Stark</string>
    <string name="background_character_stark_eddard">Eddard Stark is the head of House Stark and Lord
        Paramount of the North. The North is one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms,
        and House Stark is one of the Great Houses of the realm. House Stark rules the region from
        their seat of Winterfell, and Eddard also holds the title Lord of Winterfell. In addition,
        he is the Warden of the North. \n\n Eddard is married to Lady Catelyn of House Tully.
        Though they barely knew one another when they wed, they formed a strong and loving
        marriage. They have five legitimate children: Robb, Sansa, Arya, Bran and Rickon. Eddard
        also has an illegitimate bastard son, Jon Snow, reportedly by a common serving girl named
        Wylla. Jon&#8217;s presence at Winterfell is a source of friction between Eddard and his wife.
        Nevertheless, Eddard was close to all his children and was well-loved and respected by all
        of them. He seemed to have a soft spot for his youngest daughter, Arya. \n\n Eddard is the
        second son of Lord Rickard Stark. Lord Rickard served King Aerys II Targaryen as Warden of
        the North. Eddard&#8217;s older brother Brandon was Rickard&#8217;s heir. Eddard also has a younger
        sister Lyanna and a younger brother Benjen. Eddard is a stoic, dutiful, and honorable man
        and is considered to embody the values of the North. \n\n Eddard is a trusted, close friend
        and counselor of King Robert Baratheon. He supported Robert&#8217;s play for the throne by
        acting as a general in several major battles. Eddard&#8217;s sister Lyanna, who was betrothed to
        Robert, was kidnapped by Prince Rhaegar Targaryen, sparking the war. Brandon protested the
        kidnapping, but his attempt to bring Rhaegar to justice failed. Lord Rickard was summoned
        to court in King&#8217;s Landing by Aerys, and both Brandon and Rickard were executed by the Mad
        King. Their deaths left Eddard to inherit Rickard&#8217;s responsibilities, serving King Robert
        instead. Brandon had been betrothed to Catelyn, and Eddard also inherited his brother&#8217;s
        bride. Lyanna died in Eddard&#8217;s arms during the conflict. Despite his happy family life,
        Eddard still felt the losses of his family quite keenly, often visiting his sister&#8217;s tomb
        to light a candle for her as his daughter, Sansa, remembered. \n\n Eddard&#8217;s other younger
        sibling, Benjen, still lives and is a member of the Night&#8217;s Watch, an institution of which
        Eddard is a keen supporter. He also appeared to have troubles keeping his bannermen in
        line as Stannis Baratheon remembered his brother, Robert, saying the Northmen were
        difficult to control, even with Eddard on his side. \n\n Eddard wields a Valyrian
        greatsword named Ice (an heirloom of House Stark) which he uses on ceremonial
        occasions.</string>

    <!-- Character Stark Catelyn -->
    <string name="title_character_stark_catelyn">Catelyn Stark</string>
    <string name="background_character_stark_catelyn">Catelyn was born into House Tully and is the
        eldest child of Lord Hoster Tully. She has a younger brother, Edmure, and a younger sister,
        Lysa. Petyr Baelish was fostered with the Tullys and Catelyn grew up with him. She was
        betrothed to marry Brandon Stark of Winterfell, but he was brutally murdered by the Mad
        King, Aerys II Targaryen after Prince Rhaegar had kidnapped Brandon&#8217;s sister Lyanna.
        Catelyn instead married Brandon&#8217;s brother, Eddard. Though they barely knew one another when
        they wed they have formed a strong and loving marriage. \n\n Catelyn and Eddard have five
        children: Robb, Sansa, Arya, Bran and Rickon. She is unhappy with Eddard&#8217;s bastard son Jon
        Snow living with her family in Winterfell, the only source of friction between her and her
        husband. \n\n Catelyn has some independent political influence. A former ward of her
        father&#8217;s, Petyr Baelish, known as &#8220;Littlefinger&#8221;, is the king&#8217;s master of coin and one of
        his closest advisers in King&#8217;s Landing. \n\n Catelyn says that she hasn&#8217;t been to the
        capital city of King&#8217;s Landing since nine years before her husband went there to be the
        new Hand of the King, which would be around the time of the Greyjoy Rebellion.</string>

    <!-- Character Stark Robb -->
    <string name="title_character_stark_robb">Robb Stark</string>
    <string name="background_character_stark_robb">Robb is the eldest child of Lady Catelyn and Lord
        Eddard Stark. Eddard is the head of House Stark, Lord of Winterfell and Lord Paramount of
        the North, one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms. The Starks rule the region
        from their seat of Winterfell. Eddard is also the Warden of the North to King Robert
        Baratheon. \n\n Robb was born at Riverrun and raised in Winterfell. His father left his
        mother the morning after their wedding to fight in Robert&#8217;s Rebellion and did not return
        until after Robb was born. He has two younger trueborn brothers, Bran and Rickon, and two
        sisters, Sansa and Arya. He is also close to his bastard half-brother, Jon Snow, and to
        his father&#8217;s ward, Theon Greyjoy, whom he counts as his best friend outside of the family.
        He has been trained from childhood to wield a sword and wear armor by Winterfell&#8217;s
        Master-at-Arms Ser Rodrik Cassel, and is highly proficient with both for his young age.
        He lives at Winterfell with his family.</string>

    <!-- Character Stark Sansa -->
    <string name="title_character_stark_sansa">Sansa Stark</string>
    <string name="background_character_stark_sansa">Sansa Stark is the eldest daughter and second
        child of Lady Catelyn and Lord Eddard Stark. Eddard is the head of House Stark and Lord
        Paramount of the North. The North is one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms
        and House Stark is one of the Great Houses of the realm. House Stark rules the region from
        their seat of Winterfell and Eddard also holds the titles of Lord of Winterfell and the
        Warden of the North to King Robert Baratheon. \n\n Sansa was born and raised at Winterfell.
        She has an older brother, Robb, two younger brothers, Bran and Rickon, a younger sister,
        Arya and a bastard half-brother, Jon Snow. Sansa enjoys proper &#8220;lady-like&#8221; pursuits, and is
        good at sewing, embroidering, poetry, singing, dancing, literature and music. She dreams of
        being a regal Queen like Cersei Lannister, and that just like in the epic songs she will
        meet her knight in shining armor. She has inherited her mother&#8217;s Tully coloring, unlike
        most of her siblings, and Lady Catelyn thinks Sansa will be even more beautiful than she
        was when she was younger. She is often seen in contrast with her sister, Arya Stark who
        has neither her looks nor her accomplishments in feminine activities and
        comportment.</string>

    <!-- Character Stark Arya -->
    <string name="title_character_stark_arya">Arya Stark</string>
    <string name="background_character_stark_arya">Arya Stark is the youngest daughter and third
        child of Lady Catelyn and Lord Eddard Stark. Eddard is the head of House Stark and Lord
        Paramount of the North. The North is one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms
        and House Stark is one of the Great Houses of the realm. House Stark rules the region from
        their seat of Winterfell and Eddard also holds the title Lord of Winterfell. He is also the
        Warden of the North to King Robert Baratheon. \n\n Arya was born and raised at Winterfell.
        She has an older sister, Sansa Stark. She also has an older brother, Robb, two younger
        brothers, Bran and Rickon and a bastard half-brother, Jon Snow. \n\n Arya rejects the
        notion that she must become a lady and marry for influence and power, feeling she can
        forge her own destiny. She is fascinated by warfare and training in the use of arms, and
        is bored by embroidery and other &#8220;lady-like&#8221; pursuits. She takes after her father and has
        a quarrelsome relationship with her sister Sansa, due to their contrasting interests and
        personalities. She is close to her half-brother Jon, who is also something of an
        outcast.</string>

    <!-- Character Stark Bran -->
    <string name="title_character_stark_bran">Bran Stark</string>
    <string name="background_character_stark_bran">Bran is the fourth child and second son of Lady
        Catelyn and Lord Eddard Stark. Eddard is the head of House Stark and Lord Paramount of the
        North. The North is one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Stark is
        one of the Great Houses of the realm. House Stark rules the region from their seat of
        Winterfell and Eddard also holds the title Lord of Winterfell. He is also the Warden of
        the North to King Robert Baratheon. \n\n Bran was born and raised at Winterfell. He has an
        older brother Robb, and a younger brother Rickon. He has two older sisters, Sansa and Arya.
        He also has a bastard half-brother, Jon Snow. He is 10 years old at the start of the series.
        He was named for Eddard&#8217;s elder brother, Brandon, who was slain by the Mad King. He is only
        called &#8220;Brandon&#8221; by his mother when he has done something wrong. He dreams of being a
        knight of the Kingsguard and one day becoming a bannerman for his brother, Robb. His
        favorite hobby is climbing the walls of Winterfell and using its old rooftops and
        passageways to get around.</string>

    <!-- Character Stark Rickon -->
    <string name="title_character_stark_rickon">Bran Stark</string>
    <string name="background_character_stark_rickon">Rickon is the fifth child and youngest son of
        Lady Catelyn and Lord Eddard Stark. Eddard is the head of House Stark and Lord Paramount of
        the North. The North is one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House
        Stark is one of the Great Houses of the realm. House Stark rule the region from their seat
        of Winterfell and Eddard also holds the title Lord of Winterfell. He is also the Warden of
        the North to King Robert Baratheon. \n\n Rickon was born and raised at Winterfell. He has
        two older brothers, Robb and Bran, and two older sisters, Sansa and Arya. He also has an
        older bastard half-brother, Jon Snow. He is six-years-old when his uncle and Hand of the
        King, Lord Jon Arryn, dies.</string>

    <!-- Character Snow Jon -->
    <string name="title_character_snow_jon">Jon Snow</string>
    <string name="background_character_snow_jon">Jon is the bastard son of Lord Eddard Stark of
        Winterfell, the head of House Stark and Lord Paramount of the North. The North is one of
        the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms in Westeros, and House Stark is one of the
        Great Houses of the realm. House Stark rules the region from their seat of Winterfell and
        Eddard also holds the title Lord of Winterfell. Eddard is also the Warden of the North to King
        Robert Baratheon. \n\n Eddard once told King Robert Baratheon that Jon&#8217;s mother is a
        serving girl named Wylla, but refused to elaborate any further. Jon himself has no
        knowledge of his mother, not knowing if she&#8217;s alive or not. \n\n Jon was raised at
        Winterfell on an equal footing with Eddard&#8217;s legitimate children. He has an older
        half-brother Robb, two younger half-sisters Sansa and Arya, and two younger half-brothers
        Bran and Rickon. Jon&#8217;s presence at Winterfell is a source of friction between Eddard and
        his wife, Catelyn, although Catelyn put aside her anger temporarily when the infant Jon
        became severely ill. Jon got on well with his half-siblings, particularly Robb and
        Arya.</string>

    <!-- Character Brynden Tully -->
    <string name="title_character_tully_brynden">Brynden Tully</string>
    <string name="background_character_tully_brynden">Brynden Tully is the younger brother of
        Hoster Tully, Lord of Riverrun and head of House Tully, and the uncle of Catelyn Stark,
        Edmure Tully, and Lysa Arryn. Brynden is a respected knight and formidable battle
        commander, who first distinguished himself in the War of the Ninepenny Kings, nearly forty
        years before the War of the Five Kings. \n\n Brynden often argued with his older brother
        Hoster, particularly over the fact that Brynden never married. When Brynden returned home
        from the War of the Ninepenny Kings, Hoster had already arranged for him to marry Bethany
        Redwyne, of the wealthy and powerful House Redwyne. Brynden refused this generous match,
        however, refusing to be told when and whom to marry. Hoster was angry that Brynden would
        not do his duty to their family and enter into a marriage-alliance to improve their
        fortunes, and said that he was the black goat of the Tully herd. Brynden joked that given
        that the Tully sigil is a trout, it would be more fitting to say that he was the &#8220;black
        fish&#8221; of the Tully school. The nickname stuck, and Ser Brynden became popularly known as
        &#8220;The Blackfish&#8221; ever since. Brynden even took to using a black fish in his own personal
        heraldry: like the standard Tully heraldry it uses a red and blue background, but swaps
        out the normal silver trout for a black one. Hoster would attempt to contract other
        arranged marriage-alliances for Brynden over the years, many of them very promising
        matches, but Brynden turned down them all, which led to constant bickering between the
        two brothers throughout their lives. \n\n Despite his disagreements with his brother over
        his refusal to marry, Brynden is very devoted to his family.</string>

    <!-- Character Edmure Tully -->
    <string name="title_character_tully_edmure">Edmure Tully</string>
    <string name="background_character_tully_edmure">Ser Edmure is the son and heir of Lord Hoster
        Tully. Edmure is the new head of House Tully and thus has recently become the Lord of
        Riverrun and Lord Paramount of the Riverlands. The Riverlands are one of the constituent
        regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Tully is one of the Great Houses of the realm.
        Riverrun is the ancestral seat of House Tully. \n\n Edmure&#8217;s mother Minisa Tully died in
        childbirth during his early childhood. He has two elder sisters Catelyn and Lysa. He was
        also raised with his father&#8217;s ward, Petyr Baelish. It was Edmure who first nicknamed him
        &#8220;Littlefinger.&#8221;</string>

    <!-- Character Tywin Lannister -->
    <string name="title_character_lannister_tywin">Tywin Lannister</string>
    <string name="background_character_lannister_tywin">Tywin is the lord of House Lannister, the
        Lord Paramount of the Westerlands, and the richest man in the Seven Kingdoms. The
        Westerlands are one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Lannister
        is one of the Great Houses of the realm. House Lannister rule the region from their seat
        of Casterly Rock and Tywin also holds the title Lord of Casterly Rock. He is also the
        Warden of the West. He is a widower with three children, Jaime, Cersei and Tyrion.
        Casterly Rock, the Lannister&#8217;s ancestral seat of power, is located over a group of highly
        productive goldmines, which have provided the Lannisters with immense wealth over the years
        and led to the speculation that Tywin &#8220;shits gold.&#8221; \n\n Tywin is the son of Tytos
        Lannister. His father presided over a period of decline for the house, frittering away
        much of their fortune on poor investments and allowing himself to be mocked at court,
        creating a perception of weakness. Their vassals House Reyne of Castamere rebelled against
        Lord Tytos, and Tywin put down the rebellion personally, extinguishing their house and
        re-establishing the fearsome reputation of House Lannister. His ruthless destruction of
        House Reyne was immortalized in the song &#8220;The Rains of Castamere&#8221; and gave darker meaning
        to the common phrase &#8220;A Lannister always pays his debts,&#8221; which originally referred solely
        to the Lannister&#8217;s vast fortune. \n\n Tywin married his cousin Joanna Lannister and their
        first children were the fraternal twins Cersei and Jaime. She died after giving birth to
        Tyrion, which Tywin has blamed his son for ever since. When Jaime was diagnosed with a
        learning difficulty by a Maester who predicted that he would never read, Tywin sat with
        his son for four hours a day until he overcame his problems with transposing letters in
        his mind, much to Jaime&#8217;s resentment. Tywin despises and hates his younger son, seeing him
        as misshapen and perverse. When Tyrion was very young, Jaime set him up with a prostitute.
        Jaime posed her as a common girl in distress that they rescued from bandits. Jaime chased
        the bandits off while Tyrion comforted the girl. They married, but when Tywin found out he
        was furious and made Jaime reveal the truth. Tywin paid her for every one of his guards to
        have sex with her and forced Tyrion to watch. Tyrion&#8217;s hatred of Tywin has been
        reciprocated since. Nevertheless, all of Tywin&#8217;s children are in awe of him and heed his
        counsel. \n\n Tywin served as Hand of the King to Aerys II Targaryen for twenty years until
        the Mad King, driven by envy and distrust, rejected Tywin&#8217;s proposal to marry his daughter
        Cersei to Prince Rhaegar and made his son Jaime a member of the Kingsguard. As members of
        the Kingsguard are forbidden to marry, Aerys had effectively robbed Tywin of his heir,
        which Tywin perceived as a great insult and resigned. During Robert&#8217;s Rebellion Tywin
        remained neutral, answering neither the summons of the King nor the calls from the rebels,
        until the Battle of the Trident, after which it became clear that the rebels would win.
        Tywin marched with the full power of Casterly Rock to the capital, feigning that he had
        come to defend it from the rebellion. Aerys&#8217; advisors urged the King not to trust Tywin,
        even Jaime Lannister, who knew his father would never back the losing side in a war.
        Nevertheless, on Pycelle&#8217;s advice, the gates were opened to the Lannister army. Tywin
        ordered the city to be taken and the royal family eliminated in a quick and efficient
        manner; as a result the city was sacked and the royal family massacred by Ser Gregor
        Clegane. Upon seeing Tywin&#8217;s betrayal, Aerys ordered Jaime to bring him Tywin&#8217;s head and
        instructed his royal pyromancer to set King&#8217;s Landing ablaze. Jaime responded by
        personally stabbing the Mad King in the back. When Robert Baratheon and Eddard Stark
        reached the Red Keep, Tywin presented the bodies of the royal family as proof of his
        allegiance. After the rebellion Robert Baratheon took the throne and married Tywin&#8217;s
        daughter Cersei to cement the alliance between their houses. \n\n Cersei gave birth to
        three children--Joffrey, Myrcella, and Tommen Baratheon. Unbeknownst to Tywin all three
        children are the product of her incestuous relationship with Jaime. This was discovered by
        both Jon Arryn and Eddard Stark, albeit independently, and meant that Joffreythe oldest
        of the Baratheon children and the heir apparent to the Iron Thronehad no actual claim to
        the throne. Tywin is close to his younger brother, Kevan who is his chief advisor, and
        Kevan&#8217;s son Lancel was King Robert&#8217;s squire, and many secretly believe Lancel gave Robert
        too much wine during his fatal hunt on Cersei&#8217;s orders.</string>


    <!-- Character Cersei Lannister -->
    <string name="title_character_lannister_cersei">Cersei Lannister</string>
    <string name="background_character_lannister_cersei">Cersei is the only daughter and eldest
        child of Joanna Lannister and Lord Tywin Lannister. Tywin is the head of House Lannister,
        the richest man in the Seven Kingdoms and Lord Paramount of the Westerlands. The Westerlands
        are one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Lannister is one of the
        Great Houses of the realm. Cersei is the elder twin of Ser Jaime Lannister and the elder
        sister of Tyrion Lannister. She was raised in privilege in the family seat of Casterly Rock.
        She is noted for her great beauty. \n\n Cersei&#8217;s mother died when she was four years old,
        after giving birth to her younger brother Tyrion. Like her father, Cersei has always blamed
        Tyrion for her mother&#8217;s death and deeply resents that her mother died so that Tyrion would
        be brought into the world. Cersei&#8217;s father Tywin was constantly away from home during her
        childhood and teenaged years, serving as Hand of the King at the capital, with only
        infrequent visits back to his seat at Casterly Rock. Coupled with the death of her mother,
        this meant that Cersei and her two brothers were primarily raised by servants attached to
        House Lannister. She began an incestuous relationship with Jaime in her youth which has
        continued despite her marriage. Cersei has had other partners but Jaime has always been
        faithful to her. \n\n When she was about fifteen, Cersei and her friend Melara visited
        Maggy, a woods witch and reputed fortune teller dwelling in a hut deep in a forest close to
        Casterly Rock. Melara was reluctant, but Cersei convinced her to go. After rudely awakening
        her and insisting on having her future foretold, Maggy tasted a drop of her blood and
        revealed to Cersei she wouldn&#8217;t marry &#8220;the Prince&#8221; but &#8220;the King&#8221;, and while the king would
        have twenty sons, she would bear only three children who will wear golden crowns as well as
        golden shrouds. Finally, she revealed to Cersei that although she would indeed be Queen,
        she would be cast down by another, younger and more beautiful queen. \n\n After the end of
        the civil war which ended the reign of House Targaryen, Cersei was married to King Robert
        Baratheon, a political marriage Robert agreed to in thanks for her father&#8217;s last-minute
        alliance. She was only 19 when she married Robert and became Queen. At first, Cersei
        was infatuated with the handsome Robert, but their love begun to wane when he called her
        &#8220;Lyanna&#8221; on their wedding night. She nevertheless bore Robert a son who died shortly
        after his birth. Cersei was devastated by her son&#8217;s loss and refused to have the body taken
        from her, forcing Robert to hold her while they took her son from her. In time, Cersei&#8217;s
        feelings for Robert turned to hatred and she returned to her brother as a result. Her three
        children, Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen, are officially Robert&#8217;s, but in reality are the
        products of her incestuous relationship with Jaime.</string>

    <!-- Character Jaime Lannister -->
    <string name="title_character_lannister_jaime">Jaime Lannister</string>
    <string name="background_character_lannister_jaime">Ser Jaime Lannister is a knight of the
        Kingsguard, a position he has held for twenty years since he was a teenager, the youngest
        man ever appointed to its membership. He was appointed to the position by the Mad King,
        Aerys II Targaryen. \n\n At the conclusion of Robert&#8217;s Rebellion, Jaime&#8217;s father Tywin
        arrived at the gates of King&#8217;s Landing with the main Lannister army, pledging his
        allegiance. Most of the Small Council urged Aerys not to trust Tywin, especially Jamie,
        knowing his father would never support the losing side of a war. Instead, Grand Maester
        Pycelle gave the opposite counsel, and once the Lannister army was allowed inside, Tywin
        ordered his men to attack the city. As Lannister soldiers raped and pillaged throughout the
        city during the Sack of King&#8217;s Landing, King Aerys remained holed up inside the Red Keep,
        for hours maniacally repeating the order to &#8220;burn them all&#8221;. Despite being sworn by the
        holiest oaths to protect the king as a member of the Kingsguard, Jaime ultimately turned
        his own sword on Aerys, slaying him at the foot of the Iron Throne itself. For this
        infamous act, he is known throughout the Seven Kingdoms as the &#8220;Kingslayer&#8221;, to his
        irritation. \n\n Jaime always refused to discuss precisely what happened the day he slew
        the Mad King, and thus his true motivations and what plans Aerys had for King&#8217;s Landing
        were never revealed. On one occasion he confides the truth to Brienne of Tarth: Aerys&#8217;
        final orders were for Jaime to kill his father, and to burn the entire city and its
        inhabitants with wildfire. Unwilling to let that happen, Jaime killed him, and in doing so
        actually saved thousands of innocent lives. He adds that the &#8220;honorable&#8221; Ned Stark judged
        him guilty on the spot, without giving Jamie a chance to explain. \n\n He was forgiven for
        breaking his vows by King Robert Baratheon and permitted to remain in the Kingsguard as
        part of Robert&#8217;s alliance with House Lannister, along with the marriage of Jaime&#8217;s twin
        sister Cersei to Robert. In addition to the slaying of the Mad King, Jaime is known for
        his handsome looks, arrogant demeanor, and superb martial skills. He is so skilled with
        a sword that he claims that there are only three men in the seven kingdoms who may have a
        chance at beating him in a fair duel. \n\n Jaime is the eldest son of Joanna Lannister and
        Lord Tywin Lannister. Tywin is the head of House Lannister, the richest man in the Seven
        Kingdoms and Lord Paramount of the Westerlands. The Westerlands are one of the constituent
        regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Lannister is one of the Great Houses of the realm.
        Jaime had great difficulty learning to read as a child because he transposed letters in his
        mind. Tywin sat with him through four hours a day practicing until he learnt. Jaime
        resented being forced to spend so much time on reading. \n\n Jaime is the older brother of
        Tyrion and the twin brother of Cersei. Their mother died giving birth to Tyrion. Due to his
        place in the Kingsguard, Jaime cannot inherit his father&#8217;s lands or titles, making Tyrion
        his father&#8217;s heir; a fact which vexes Tywin. Unlike Cersei and Tywin, Jaime always treated
        Tyrion with a degree of kindness and respect. In a secret known to only a few, Jaime is
        Cersei&#8217;s lover and the biological father of her children, Joffrey, Myrcella, and Tommen,
        whom the world believes are Robert&#8217;s kin.</string>

    <!-- Character Tyrion Lannister -->
    <string name="title_character_lannister_tyrion">Tyrion Lannister</string>
    <string name="background_character_lannister_tyrion">Tyrion Lannister is the youngest son of
        Joanna Lannister and Lord Tywin Lannister. Tywin is the head of House Lannister, the
        richest man in the Seven Kingdoms and Lord Paramount of the Westerlands. The Westerlands
        are one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Lannister of Casterly
        Rock is one of the Great Houses of the realm. He is the younger brother of Jaime and Cersei
        Lannister. His mother Joanna Lannister died giving birth to him. His father and sister hold
        him in contempt as they blame him for the death. \n\n He is a dwarf, causing him problems
        and persecution. His size has led him to being referred to derisively by various names,
        such as &#8220;The Imp&#8221; and &#8220;The Halfman&#8221;. This is mitigated by his intellect and his family&#8217;s
        wealth and power. Had an infant with dwarfism like Tyrion been born a commoner, he&#8217;d have
        simply been left out in the woods to die. However, Tyrion was born into a powerful noble
        House, and was therefore spared. Even though his father doesn&#8217;t think much of him, he has
        had the benefits of being raised with wealth and education, and is expected to lead his
        life as a credit to the Lannister name. He is committed to the good of both his House
        and, since Cersei married King Robert Baratheon, his family&#8217;s continued hold on the throne.
        \n\n When Tyrion was 16, he met a wheelwright&#8217;s daughter named Tysha on the road,
        apparently the victim of an attempted rape. While his brother Jaime ran off the attackers,
        Tyrion helped Tysha recover from the ordeal, and they became lovers. They found a drunken,
        wandering septon willing to marry them and briefly, they lived as husband and wife. That
        is, until Lord Tywin learned what had happened. Jaime confessed that he organized the
        incident to make his brother happy, and Tysha was actually a prostitute. As a lesson, Tywin
        gave Tysha to his guards, paying her a silver coin for each man and forcing Tyrion to watch.
        By the end, there were so many silver coins that they were running out of her hands onto
        the ground. Tyrion has reciprocated Tywin&#8217;s hatred ever since. \n\n His two siblings have
        had positions of respect and responsibility since their teens. When Tyrion turned sixteen
        (the age of manhood), Tywin Lannister put Tyrion in charge of the drains and cisterns at
        Casterly Rock. Tyrion brags that the &#8220;[sewage] never flowed [smoother] to the sea.&#8221; \n\n
        Tyrion once encountered Lord Gregor Forrester at the Tourney in Lannisport. While they once
        spoke briefly, Tyrion found Gregor very honorable, even mentioning it to Gregor&#8217;s daughter
        Mira years later. \n\n Tyrion spends a lot of time at court in King&#8217;s Landing to avoid his
        father. He gets on well with Jaime and his niece Myrcella and nephew Tommen, but has a
        colder relationship with Cersei and his sadistic nephew Joffrey. He has a fondness for
        prostitutes and drink, but is also intelligent, cunning, and educated. He also is a kind
        man who would protect the innocent claiming that he loves broken things.</string>

    <!-- Character Joffrey Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_joffrey">Joffrey Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_joffrey">Joffrey is believed to be the oldest son
        and heir of King Robert Baratheon and Queen Cersei Lannister, both of whom entered into a
        political marriage alliance after Robert took the throne by force from the Mad King Aerys
        II Targaryen. In reality, his father is Jaime Lannister, the queen&#8217;s brother and the Lord
        Commander of the Kingsguard. He has a younger sister, Myrcella, and a younger brother,
        Tommen , both whom are also the product of Jaime and Cersei&#8217;s incest. Their sole biological
        grandparents, Tywin and Joanna Lannister, were also apparently first cousins. \n\n Joffrey
        takes after his mother in terms of looks and personality, his blonde hair being a subtle
        clue that he isn&#8217;t really a Baratheon, who famously always possess black hair even when
        one of their parents possesses blonde hair. (Cersei herself lets it slip to Catelyn Stark
        that she once had a child with black hair who died prematurely before she had Joffrey.) He
        is usually accompanied by his sworn shield, the formidable Sandor Clegane, better known as
        the Hound. Even before he ascends to the Iron Throne, Joffrey is spoiled, arrogant,
        cowardly, and sadistic; however these traits are further exacerbated upon Robert&#8217;s death
        and his ascension to the crown.</string>

    <!-- Character Myrcella Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_myrcella">Myrcella Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_myrcella">Princess Myrcella was commonly thought
        to be the only daughter of King Robert Baratheon and Queen Cersei Lannister. Cersei and
        Robert married to seal a political alliance between House Baratheon and House Lannister
        after Robert took the throne by force from the Mad King Aerys II Targaryen. Myrcella had an
        older brother, Joffrey, and a younger, Tommen, with whom she was close. The real father of
        all three children is Jaime Lannister, her uncle (Cersei&#8217;s twin brother) and a member of
        the Kingsguard, making them bastards born of incest. However, like her siblings and the
        rest of Westeros, Myrcella had no idea of the truth of her parentage at the time. She had a
        sweet and quiet disposition and was fond of her uncle Tyrion Lannister.</string>

    <!-- Character Tommen Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_tommen">Tommen Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_tommen">Tommen is presented as the youngest son of
        King Robert Baratheon and Queen Cersei Lannister. Cersei and Robert made a political
        marriage alliance after Robert took the throne by force from the Mad King Aerys II
        Targaryen. Tommen&#8217;s real father is Jaime Lannister, his mother&#8217;s twin brother and his uncle.
        \n\n He has an older brother, Joffrey, and an older sister Myrcella with the same
        obfuscated parentage. Tommen is good-natured and passive in contrast to his brother
        Joffrey, who sometimes bullied Tommen for amusement. Like his sister, he is fond of his
        uncle Tyrion.</string>

    <!-- Character Kevan Lannister -->
    <string name="title_character_lannister_kevan">Kevan Lannister</string>
    <string name="background_character_lannister_kevan">Kevan is the second son of the late Lord
        Tytos Lannister. He is the brother of Lord Tywin Lannister the head of House Lannister
        and Lord of Casterly Rock. Kevan is married to Dorna Lannister and they have a son Lancel,
        who is a squire to King Robert Baratheon. He is a noted knight who served his elder brother
        loyally as an adviser, and is respected for his wise and candid counsel.</string>

    <!-- Character Lancel Lannister -->
    <string name="title_character_lannister_lancel">Lancel Lannister</string>
    <string name="background_character_lannister_lancel">Lancel Lannister is the son of Ser Kevan
        Lannister and the nephew of Lord Tywin Lannister, the head of House Lannister and Lord of
        Casterly Rock. He is the first cousin of Jaime, Cersei, and Tyrion Lannister. He has the
        familial blond hair and resembles his cousin Jaime. He is a squire to King Robert
        Baratheon.</string>

    <!-- Character Bronn -->
    <string name="title_character_bronn">Bronn</string>
    <string name="background_character_bronn">Bronn is a sellsword; a mercenary soldier whose
        service as a warrior is for hire. Not much is known about his past or family. Both his
        parents beat him, and his nose was accidentally broken when his mother hit him with
        kitchenware, which she had meant for Bronn&#8217;s younger brother. When Tyrion Lannister
        introduced him to Tywin Lannister, Bronn said that his father is no one Lord Tywin would
        know. During a drinking game with Tyrion and Shae, Bronn claims that he killed a woman
        before he was 12 years old, though it was in self-defense as she was attacking him with an
        axe. Bronn also confirmed Tyrion&#8217;s claim that Bronn has been beyond the Wall. When asked
        why he was there, he bluntly answers that it was &#8220;work&#8221;.</string>

    <!-- Character Qyburn -->
    <string name="title_character_qyburn">Qyburn</string>
    <string name="background_character_qyburn">Qyburn is a former maester of the Citadel. He was
        stripped of his chain by the Archmaesters for engaging in forbidden human experimentation:
        it was discovered that he had been vivisecting living men in his pursuit of medical
        knowledge. Qyburn held to the belief that the death of a few men was justifiable if it
        would lead to medical breakthroughs that would save the lives of many more. \n\n While his
        unethical experiments have led to him being reviled, they also made him arguably one of
        the most talented healers in all of Westeros.</string>

    <!-- Character Pycelle -->
    <string name="title_character_pycelle">Pycelle</string>
    <string name="background_character_pycelle">Pycelle has been Grand Maester of the Seven
        Kingdoms for decades and has served under four kings when the series begins. The Grand
        Maester is the King&#8217;s personal maester, a learned man wise in history, science and
        medicine who also provides counsel. The Grand Maester sits on the King&#8217;s small council,
        which runs the realm in the name of the King. He served King Aerys II Targaryen prior to
        Robert&#8217;s Rebellion. He remembers Aerys as a great man before his descent into madness.
        When Tywin Lannister marched to the gates of King&#8217;s Landing following the rebel victory at
        the Battle of the Trident and all of the King&#8217;s advisors told Aerys not to trust the Lord
        of Casterly Rock, Pycelle gave the opposite counsel and the city gates were opened,
        allowing the Lannister forces to sack the capital. \n\n Following the rebellion he remained
        Grand Maester to King Robert Baratheon. He is joined on the small council by the Master of C
        oin Petyr Baelish, also called Littlefinger, the Master of Whisperers Varys, the Master of
        Ships Stannis Baratheon and the Master of Laws Renly Baratheon. He plays up his age to
        appear harmless but is actually mentally sharp and dangerous. He is loyal to Queen Cersei
        Lannister and was involved in the birth of all of her children, assisted by midwives.
        Pycelle also privately flouts the vow of celibacy taken by maesters, as he enjoys the
        company of prostitutes such as Ros. Despite his tendency for deception, he does retain some
        sense of medical ethics, as he found Qyburn&#8217;s methods abhorrent.</string>

    <!-- Character Petyr Baelish -->
    <string name="title_character_baelish_petyr">Petyr Baelish</string>
    <string name="background_character_baelish_petyr">Petyr Baelish is the head of House Baelish,
        and the lord of an extremely minor holding, so small it has neither name nor maester,
        located in a small area within the Fingers, a coastal region in the northeastern shores of
        the Vale of Arryn. He is currently House Baelish&#8217;s only living member. \n\n House Baelish
        had very meager origins and no distinguished lineage: Petyr&#8217;s great-grandfather was a
        lowly sellsword from Braavos who came to the Vale at the invitation of House Corbray.
        Petyr&#8217;s grandfather was a poor hedge knight, who managed to earn a minor lordship of a few
        stony acres in the smallest peninsula of the Fingers. \n\n Petyr&#8217;s father fought in the War
        of the Ninepenny Kings, the preemptive assault on the forces of Maelys Blackfyre, the last
        of the Blackfyre Pretenders, before they could attempt an invasion of Westeros. During the
        conflict Petyr&#8217;s father served well under Lord Hoster Tully. Through their good
        relationship Hoster agreed to foster his son Petyr at Riverrun, a great honor for a lesser
        House. \n\n Petyr went to Riverrun when he was eight years old, carrying all he owned in a
        bundle. At Riverrun he befriended Hoster&#8217;s daughters Catelyn and Lysa Tully. Their brother
        Edmure mockingly nicknamed him &#8220;Littlefinger&#8221; at the time, in reference to his small height
        at the time and the location of his minor landholdings. The nickname would stick with him
        throughout his life. Eventually even Petyr sarcastically embraced the nickname, due to the
        fact that it demonstrated how far he had risen, from an impoverished noble-born boy from an
        insignificant minor House in the &#8220;little Finger&#8221; peninsula of the Vale, to one of the most
        powerful officials at the royal court. \n\n Petyr became smitten with Catelyn but she never
        returned his affections. Lysa was infatuated with Petyr, but he only loved Catelyn.
        Eventually when she was betrothed to Brandon Stark, heir to Lord of Winterfell and Lord
        Paramount of the North, Petyr challenged him to a duel, thinking he could win through pluck
        and courage - he was promptly overpowered and nearly killed, though Catelyn begged Brandon
        to spare his life. Embittered, Petyr was cast out of Riverrun and returned to the Vale.
        During the course of Robert&#8217;s Rebellion, however, Brandon was killed by the Mad King Aerys
        II Targaryen, so Catelyn married his younger brother Eddard Stark, while to secure a
        political alliance Lysa was wed to Jon Arryn, ruler of the Vale. Manipulating Lysa&#8217;s
        infatuation with himself, Petyr ingratiated himself into Jon&#8217;s services, first as customs
        officer at Gulltown, where he increased the port&#8217;s revenues tenfold. Seeing Littlefinger&#8217;s
        financial acumen, Jon was easily convinced by Lysa to later bring Littlefinger to the royal
        court at King&#8217;s Landing, and make him Master of Coin on King Robert Baratheon&#8217;s Small
        Council. Baelish&#8217;s naked ambition often placed him at odds with the Master of Whisperers,
        Lord Varys. In charge of the crown&#8217;s treasury, Littlefinger rapidly grew into a powerful
        player in royal politics and a master of court intrigues. Of an older mindset, few who did
        not know him suspected Littlefinger as a threat, seeing only that he was a man from a very
        minor House, with no distinguished lineage, significant landholdings, or armies. Instead,
        Littlefinger based his newfound power on money. Baelish is unscrupulous in his search
        for power and wealth: he has bought multiple brothels in the city - particularly a high
        class brothel catering to the nobles in the city - cynically noting that whores make a
        better investment than ships, because they rarely sink. Baelish makes good use of his
        brothels to have his agents spy on and manipulate his clientele, and owns one of the
        largest spy networks in Westeros - second only to Varys&#8217;s. Littlefinger has been known to
        privately bribe lords who have unusual or violent sexual fetishes if they pay the right
        price - ranging from supplying lords with amputee prostitutes, to delivering young boys to
        pederasts, and even delivering prostitutes to be secretly murdered by his clients for
        thrill-kills. \n\n Due to their past friendship as children, Catelyn Stark continued to
        believe that Lord Baelish was a friend she could count on at court.</string>

    <!-- Character Varys -->
    <string name="title_character_varys">Varys</string>
    <string name="background_character_varys">Varys was born across the Narrow Sea in Lys. He was
        born a slave, and as a child he traveled with a troupe of actors all around the different
        Free Cities until a sorcerer in the city of Myr made an offer Varys&#8217;s master couldn&#8217;t
        refuse. Varys was sold to the sorcerer, who gave him a potion that made him unable to move
        or speak but didn&#8217;t dull his perceptions or sense of pain, and emasculated him (cutting off
        his testes and penis both) so he could use his sexual organs in a magical ritual, burning
        them in a brazier. When the sorcerer had thrown Varys&#8217;s genitals in the brazier, the fire
        turned blue and a voice replied back. Afterward, the sorcerer had no more use for Varys and
        threw him in the streets to die. Instead, Varys resolved to live no matter what: begging,
        stealing, and selling the sexual use of what parts remained to him, doing anything to
        survive. He also became an excellent thief, but soon learned that stolen information was
        often a far more valuable commodity than any physical goods, and he worked his way up from
        the slums of Myr. He became a master spy and information trafficker, and his influence and
        reputation grew so great that he eventually found himself as a member of the Small Council
        in the Seven Kingdoms. His experience at the hands of the sorcerer had also left him with
        a bitter hatred for magic and its practitioners. \n\n As a member of the King&#8217;s Small
        Council, he serves as the Master of Whisperers, the King&#8217;s foremost spymaster and
        intelligence agent. He holds no inherited title, castle, or lands in Westeros, but is
        called &#8220;Lord&#8221; as a courtesy due to his position on the council, which traditionally is
        made up of high lords. \n\n When the Mad King arrested Brandon Stark for threatening Prince
        Rhaegar, Varys and the rest of the Small Council urged the King to pardon Brandon on the
        grounds that he was the heir to Winterfell and the Prince had abducted his sister. However,
        the King refused to heed their advice and had both Brandon and his father brutally
        executed. This led to a rebellion that ultimately toppled the Targaryen dynasty. \n\n When
        the Mad King&#8217;s former Hand Tywin Lannister arrived at King&#8217;s Landing with the entire
        Lannister army at his back, professing loyalty to his beleaguered King after the rebels&#8217;
        resounding victory at the Battle of the Trident, Varys warned Aerys not to open the gates,
        as did Tywin&#8217;s own son in the Kingsguard, Jaime Lannister. However, Grand Maester Pycelle
        told Aerys what he wanted to hear: that he could trust Lord Tywin. So Aerys opened the
        gates and Tywin sacked the city, and Jaime wound up stabbing Aerys in the back. \n\n Despite
        his previous loyalty to the Targaryens, Varys was pardoned by the new King Robert Baratheon
        and allowed to keep his position on the Small Council under the advice of his Hand, Jon
        Arryn. \n\n Varys is bald and tends towards fat, due to his castration. He often puts on
        the public persona of being nothing more than a pudgy man well suited to the pleasantries
        of court life; humble, obsequious, fawning, and a little effeminate. This is simply a
        facade that Varys has developed, which often leads those who do not know him well to
        underestimate him as a cheerful and vapid flatterer. In reality he is a cunning and
        ruthless manipulator of court politics, on-par with Master of Coin Petyr &#8220;Littlefinger&#8221;
        Baelish, with whom he frequently spars. Unlike Baelish, Varys insists that his goals are
        to achieve what he honestly feels is best for the realm, though of course, what he and the
        current King feel is best might be two separate things. \n\n He is disparagingly known as
        &#8220;The Spider&#8221; due to his vast web of intelligence sources. His sophisticated intelligence
        network - one of the largest in the world - spans both Westeros and Essos, as far as Vaes
        Dothrak and even Qarth. He refers to his agents and sources of information- many of which
        are low-born children- as his &#8220;little birds&#8221;. Unlike Baelish, however, Varys is not
        indifferent or cruel towards his employees; he educates them and provides them with
        protection in return for the information they bring him. \n\n One of his jobs is to keep an
        eye on the movements of Viserys and Daenerys Targaryen and ensure they do not become a
        threat to King Robert&#8217;s reign.</string>

    <!-- Character Margaery Tyrell -->
    <string name="title_character_tyrell_margaery">Margaery Tyrell</string>
    <string name="background_character_tyrell_margaery">Margaery is the only daughter of Lady
        Alerie Tyrell and Lord Mace Tyrell, the Lord Paramount of the Reach. The Reach is one of
        the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Tyrell is one of the Great Houses
        of the realm. Margaery was raised in privilege in the family seat and regional capital of
        Highgarden. She is close to her brother, Ser Loras Tyrell, the Knight of Flowers. She is
        also close to her handmaidens, Sera Durwell and Mira Forrester, who followed her to King&#8217;s
        Landing from Highgarden. She is said to be as beautiful as she is clever.</string>

    <!-- Character Loras Tyrell -->
    <string name="title_character_tyrell_loras">Loras Tyrell</string>
    <string name="background_character_tyrell_loras">Ser Loras Tyrell is the son of Lady Alerie
        Hightower and Lord Mace Tyrell, the Lord Paramount of the Reach and Warden of the South.
        The Reach is one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Tyrell is one
        of the Great Houses of the realm. Loras was raised in privilege in the family seat and
        regional capital of Highgarden. Loras is the heir to Highgarden and the Tyrell lands and
        titles, and this status, along with his skills and good looks, makes him possibly the most
        sought-after bachelor in all of Westeros. \n\n Loras is a skilled knight famed for his many
        tournament victories and his good looks, which make him popular with the smallfolk and with
        young women in particular. Loras is one of the few knights who has on rare occasion managed
        to defeat the formidable Jaime Lannister in a joust. He is commonly known as the &#8220;Knight of
        the Flowers&#8221;, as a rose is the sigil of House Tyrell and he thus wears armor elaborately
        engraved with flowers. \n\n Loras is the former squire of Lord Renly Baratheon and remains
        Renly&#8217;s close friend and lover. When the series begins Loras is in King&#8217;s Landing primarily
        to compete in tourneys and attend court.</string>

    <!-- Character Olenna Tyrell -->
    <string name="title_character_tyrell_olenna">Olenna Tyrell</string>
    <string name="background_character_tyrell_olenna">Olenna Tyrell is the widow of Lord Luthor
        Tyrell and the mother of Mace Tyrell, the current Lord of Highgarden, Warden of the South,
        Lord Paramount of the Reach, and head of House Tyrell. She is the grandmother of his
        children Loras and Margaery. She was born into House Redwyne, one of the most prominent and
        powerful vassals of House Tyrell. \n\n In her youth, Olenna Redwyne was engaged to a member
        of House Targaryen, as it was &#8220;all the rage&#8221; at the time; it was her sister Viola whom
        Luthor Tyrell was expected to marry. The night before Luthor was to propose to Viola,
        Olenna snuck into his chamber and seduced him, leaving him &#8220;unable to walk downstairs&#8221;
        the next day to propose to Viola. Olenna did this because the thought of marrying a
        Targaryen and his &#8220;ludicrous silver hair&#8221; did not appeal to her. \n\n Although Olenna
        consistently referred to Luthor as an oaf, she was genuinely fond of him, and confided
        to Margaery that she had some difficulty accepting his death after his body was delivered
        to her.</string>

    <!-- Character Mace Tyrell -->
    <string name="title_character_tyrell_mace">Mace Tyrell</string>
    <string name="background_character_tyrell_mace">Mace Tyrell is the Lord of Highgarden and head
        of House Tyrell, one of the Great Houses of Westeros. He is the Lord Paramount of the Reach
        and Warden of the South. The Tyrells are one of the richest and most powerful families in
        Westeros, second only to the Lannisters - for while the mountains of the Westerlands
        possess rich gold mines, the fields of The Reach are the most fertile in Westeros, capable
        of supporting armies almost twice the size of any other kingdom. \n\n Mace is not
        considered a great strategist or general himself - his own mother Olenna openly describes
        him as an oaf. On the other hand, he has shown good judgment in delegating such tasks to
        trusted, skilled subordinates, such as the famous general Randyll Tarly, who often commands
        Mace&#8217;s forces in battle. \n\n Mace might not be the most intelligent man, but he is an
        amiable fellow well-liked by most of his bannermen, as well a loving husband and father.
        Mace has one son, Loras, and a daughter, Margaery, arguably the most eligible woman in the
        Seven Kingdoms. Mace hopes to make a good match for her to increase the already
        considerable power and influence of his family. Mace is particularly eager for Margaery to
        secure a royal marriage for their family because unlike some of the other Great Houses of
        the Seven Kingdoms such as the Starks or Lannisters, the Tyrells never ruled as kings in
        their own right, but were granted control of the Reach as a reward for submitting to Aegon
        the Conqueror during the Targaryen Conquest three hundred years ago. Thus entering into the
        royal bloodline would increase House Tyrell&#8217;s prestige and secure their rule over their
        fractious vassals in the Reach. \n\n During Robert&#8217;s Rebellion, Mace and House Tyrell
        stayed loyal to House Targaryen. The Tyrells owed their rule over Highgarden and the Reach
        to the Targaryen kings, who after the Targaryen Conquest three centuries before had awarded
        rule of the Reach to the Tyrells ahead of other families from the region which actually had
        better claims (such as House Florent). The Tyrell armies were able to inflict the only
        defeat that Robert Baratheon suffered during the entire war at the Battle of Ashford.
        Afterwards, Mace&#8217;s massive army moved east to lay siege to the mighty castle-seat of the
        Baratheons, Storm&#8217;s End. The Siege of Storm&#8217;s End lasted the better part of a year, while
        Mace and his commanders feasted in sight of the starving garrison led by Robert&#8217;s younger
        brother Stannis. Ultimately Stannis&#8217;s determined defense held, and the siege only succeeded
        in pinning down Mace&#8217;s army and preventing it from assisting the Targaryens in the
        climactic battles occurring further north. After the Sack of King&#8217;s Landing, Eddard Stark
        rode south with the main rebel army to relieve the siege. With the capital city in rebel
        hands, and both Prince Rhaegar Targaryen and his father Mad King Aerys dead, Mace saw that
        the war was clearly lost and gave no battle to Lord Eddard. Instead he peacefully dipped
        his banners and submitted to Robert&#8217;s rule, and in return was treated leniently, pardoned,
        and allowed to continue ruling the Reach as his family had before the war. However, ever
        since there was never any great love between Mace Tyrell and Stannis Baratheon.</string>

    <!-- Character Roose Bolton -->
    <string name="title_character_bolton_roose">Roose Bolton</string>
    <string name="background_character_bolton_roose">Roose Bolton is the head of House Bolton, a
        vassal family to House Stark of Winterfell. He is the Lord of the Dreadfort. Roose takes
        pride in his house sigil; the flayed man. Although torture is outlawed in the North, his
        family is famous for flaying the skin from their enemies as a means of torture and
        execution. Roose fought for Lord Eddard Stark in the civil war against House Targaryen
        known as Robert&#8217;s Rebellion and proved his worth as a soldier in the Battle of the Trident.
        He advised Robert Baratheon to execute Ser Barristan Selmy, a legendary Kingsguard sworn to
        the Targaryens, but Robert overruled Roose and pardoned Selmy. \n\n Roose Bolton had a
        trueborn son, Domeric, who perished, forcing Roose to rely on his bastard son, Ramsay
        Snow.</string>

    <!-- Character Ramsay Bolton -->
    <string name="title_character_bolton_ramsay">Ramsay Bolton</string>
    <string name="background_character_bolton_ramsay">Ramsay Snow, better known as &#8220;The Bastard of
        Bolton&#8221;, is Lord Roose Bolton&#8217;s bastard son and the product of rape: years ago Roose
        discovered that a miller had wed without his permission. He had the miller hanged and
        raped his wife. Ramsay was born shortly afterwards, and his mother brought him to the
        Dreadfort, his father&#8217;s castle, for Roose to acknowledge as his son. Roose very nearly
        killed both Ramsay and his mother, but relented upon realizing that the child was indeed
        his. \n\n Ramsay is Roose&#8217;s only living child following the death of Domeric Bolton, as
        well as the only possible heir to House Bolton until the birth of a child by Roose&#8217;s new
        wife, Fat Walda Frey. He stayed behind as castellan of the Dreadfort when his father left
        for the south to fight in the War of the Five Kings. \n\n Ramsay keeps a pack of dogs,
        which he employs for hunting. He is also in a relationship with the kennelmaster&#8217;s
        daughter, Myranda, whom he supposedly planned to marry before his father ultimately had
        him legitimized.</string>

    <!-- Character Theon Greyjoy -->
    <string name="title_character_greyjoy_theon">Theon Greyjoy</string>
    <string name="background_character_greyjoy_theon">Theon is the youngest son of Lord Balon and
        Lady Alannys Greyjoy. Balon is the head of House Greyjoy and Lord of the Iron Islands. The
        Iron Islands are one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Greyjoy is
        one of the Great Houses of the realm. House Greyjoy rule the region from their seat at Pyke
        and Balon also holds the title Lord Reaper of Pyke. \n\n Theon was born at Pyke. He is
        Balon and Alannys&#8217; fourth child after Rodrik, Maron, and Yara. Eight years before the
        start of the series Balon rose in rebellion against the Iron Throne. The ironborn were
        crushed in a war led by King Robert Baratheon and Lord Eddard Stark. Theon&#8217;s brothers were
        both killed in the fighting. Balon surrendered and was allowed to remain Lord of the Iron
        Islands on the condition that Theon remain a hostage and ward of Eddard Stark. Theon&#8217;s
        sister Yara remained on the Iron Islands. Despite his status as a hostage at Winterfell,
        Theon was treated well by the Starks, and he came to see Eddard as a surrogate father,
        while becoming best friends with Robb Stark. Theon is a skilled archer. His cocky arrogance
        and cavalier actions contrast with the staid ways of the North.</string>

    <!-- Character Walda Bolton -->
    <string name="title_character_bolton_walda">Walda Bolton</string>
    <string name="background_character_bolton_walda">Walda is a member of House Frey and a
        granddaughter of Lord Walder Frey.</string>

    <!-- Character Walder Frey -->
    <string name="title_character_frey_walter">Walder Frey</string>
    <string name="background_character_frey_walter">Walder Frey is the Lord of the Crossing and the
        head of House Frey, a vassal family of House Tully of the Riverlands. His house is noted
        for its overwhelming fertility and he has over one hundred descendents. He rules The Twins
        and its surrounding lands, controlling the strategically important crossing of the Green
        Fork.  Over the years this great stone bridge and the castles that control it have made
        House Frey a fortune in crossing fees. He has been married seven times and is almost ninety
        years old when the series begins. \n\n He is referred to by his liege lord, Hoster Tully,
        as the &#8220;Late Lord Frey&#8221; after delaying his arrival to assist Robert&#8217;s Rebellion until the
        outcome had already been determined.</string>

    <!-- Character Lothar Frey -->
    <string name="title_character_frey_lothar">Lothar Frey</string>
    <string name="background_character_frey_lothar">Lothar is a son of Walder Frey, the Lord of the
        Crossing. He is the steward of the Twins, managing the day-to-day running of the castle.
        He often plans and organizes the fine details to achieve his father&#8217;s goals.</string>

    <!-- Character Walder Rivers -->
    <string name="title_character_rivers_walder">Walder Rivers</string>
    <string name="background_character_rivers_walder">Walder is known as &#8220;Black Walder&#8221; for his
        temper and demeanor. He is a bastard son of his namesake Lord Walder Frey, Lord of the
        Crossing and head of House Frey.</string>

    <!-- Character Roslin Frey -->
    <string name="title_character_frey_roslin">Roslin Frey</string>
    <string name="background_character_frey_roslin">Roslin is the 19-year-old daughter of Lord
        Walder Frey, Lord of the Crossing. Unlike the majority of Lord Walder&#8217;s brood, Roslin is
        quite beautiful. She was intended to marry King Robb Stark as part of an alliance between
        her father and him (Walder had given Robb a choice of any one of his many daughters or
        granddaughters, but Roslin would have been the obvious choice), but Robb fell in love
        with and married Talisa Maegyr instead.</string>

    <!-- Character Robert Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_robert">Robert Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_robert">Robert is the first son of Steffon
        Baratheon and Cassana Baratheon, and has two younger brothers, Renly and Stannis. Steffon
        was the head of House Baratheon and Lord Paramount of the Stormlands. The Stormlands are
        one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Baratheon is one of the
        Great Houses of the realm. His parents died in his youth when their ship was caught in a
        storm; Robert, standing on the walls of Storm&#8217;s End with Stannis, witnessed his parents
        ship that was returning from Essos break up on the rocks. He inherited the lordship, and
        was fostered by Jon Arryn, the head of House Arryn, another Great House. Eddard Stark, the
        second son of House Stark, was also fostered by Jon Arryn and Robert and Eddard became as
        close as brothers. \n\n Robert served King Aerys II Targaryen (known as the Mad King) as
        the Lord Paramount of the Stormlands. Robert was betrothed to Lyanna Stark, Eddard&#8217;s sister.
        Lyanna was kidnapped by Prince Rhaegar Targaryen. \n\n The mad king had Eddard&#8217;s father and
        brother killed for protesting against the kidnapping. Their deaths sparked a massive
        uprising against Aerys led by Robert, Eddard and Jon Arryn. Lyanna and Aerys died during
        the civil war that followed. Robert claimed the Iron Throne because he started the war and
        killed Prince Rhaegar personally. Robert also had the best claim to the throne as a result
        of being related to the Targaryens through his paternal grandmother, Rhaelle Targaryen. The
        other leaders of the rebels, Jon Arryn and Eddard Stark, believed that Robert, with his
        claim and charismatic personality, should be king and both stood aside. \n\n Robert was
        devastated by Lyanna&#8217;s death, but was urged by Jon Arryn to marry Cersei of House Lannister,
        making an alliance with her father, Tywin Lannister, who had joined his cause late in the
        conflict and delivered the capital of King&#8217;s Landing to him. He named Jon Arryn as his Hand
        while Eddard took his father&#8217;s role as Warden of the North. \n\n Stannis fought for Robert
        through the war though the two brothers never loved each other. Despite Stannis&#8217; service
        during the war, Robert made Renly the Lord of Storm&#8217;s End following his victory. Renly was
        only a child during the war, so he did not fight. Stannis was made Lord of Dragonstone and
        served on Robert&#8217;s small council as Master of Ships. Renly later joined the small council
        as Master of Laws. \n\n Robert has been the King of the Andals and the First Men and the
        ruler of the Seven Kingdoms of Westeros since the end of the civil war. However, he is more
        interested in drinking, whoring and hunting than ruling his kingdom. He revels in the glory
        days of the rebellion. He leaves running the kingdom largely to his small council, led by
        Jon Arryn. King Robert also loves to throw events such as tournaments at which he spares no
        expense. Unfortunately, after seventeen years Robert&#8217;s excesses have left the realm deeply
        in debt for a shocking six million Gold Dragons, half to House Lannister. He apparently has
        three children with Cersei: Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen. Unbeknownst to Robert, all three
        were actually fathered by Cersei&#8217;s twin brother Jaime Lannister. Robert has also fathered
        several illegitimate bastards, to whom he pays no attention. He has an unacknowledged
        bastard son named Gendry fathered on a tavern wench. He has an unacknowledged bastard
        daughter named Barra fathered on the prostitute Mhaegen. He has at least four other
        unacknowledged bastards fathered with various women in the city of King&#8217;s Landing alone.
        \n\n Jon Arryn began investigating the lineage of Cersei&#8217;s children, comparing their
        appearance to Robert&#8217;s bastard offspring. He died under mysterious circumstances shortly
        after beginning his investigation. Robert has decided to ride north to Eddard&#8217;s keep
        Winterfell to name him as Jon Arryn&#8217;s replacement.</string>

    <!-- Character Stannis Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_stannis">Stannis Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_stannis">Stannis is the second born son of
        Steffon Baratheon and Cassana Baratheon, the younger brother of the late King Robert
        Baratheon and older brother of Renly Baratheon. Steffon was the head of House Baratheon
        and Lord Paramount of the Stormlands. The Stormlands are one of the constituent regions
        of the Seven Kingdoms and House Baratheon is one of the Great Houses of the realm. Steffon
        died when the boys were young and Robert inherited his titles. Stannis is a serious and
        severe man. \n\n Robert led a rebellion against King Aerys II Targaryen, deposing and
        replacing him as the ruler of the Seven Kingdoms. Stannis fought for Robert during the war.
        He was besieged at Storm&#8217;s End for much of the conflict. He was rescued from starvation by
        the smuggler Davos, who brought a ship full of onions into the castle. Stannis knighted
        Davos as a reward but also punished him for his smuggling by cutting four finger tips from
        his right hand. Davos is fiercely loyal to Stannis and saw his punishment as just. Davos&#8217;s
        son Matthos served Stannis as a scribe. Stannis went on to conquer Dragonstone, the seat
        of House Targaryen. During the Greyjoy Rebellion, Stannis destroyed the Greyjoy fleet. \n\n
        Stannis and Robert never loved one another. Despite Stannis&#8217; service during the war, Robert
        made Renly the Lord of Storm&#8217;s End following his victory. Renly was only a child during the
        civil war, so he did not fight. Stannis was made Prince of Dragonstone and served on his
        brother&#8217;s small council as Master of Ships. Though not outright cruel or malicious, he is a
        stern and humorless man, making him the least popular of the Baratheon brothers. \n\n He
        married Selyse Florent. They have a loveless marriage; Stannis regards her as sickly and
        resents her failure to bear him a son. During the first season Stannis is on Dragonstone
        for an extended stay, preferring the solitude of the island. \n\n He has converted to the
        Lord of Light under the influence of the priestess Melisandre. His household have largely
        followed his conversion. He has adopted the flaming red heart of the Lord of Light with
        the stag of Baratheon in the middle as his sigil.</string>

    <!-- Character Renly Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_renly">Renly Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_renly">Renly is the third and youngest son of
        Steffon and Cassana Baratheon. Steffon was the head of House Baratheon and Lord Paramount
        of the Stormlands. The Stormlands are one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms
        and House Baratheon is one of the Great Houses of the realm. Renly has two older brothers
        Robert and Stannis. Their parents died when the boys were young and Robert inherited his
        father&#8217;s titles. Robert led a rebellion against King Aerys II Targaryen, deposing and
        replacing him as the King on the Iron Throne. He made Renly the Lord of Storm&#8217;s End
        following his victory. Renly was only a child during the civil war, so he did not fight.
        \n\n Renly serves Robert as Master of Laws on the King&#8217;s small council in King&#8217;s Landing.
        He is fourth in line to the throne, behind his nephews Joffrey and Tommen and his older
        brother Stannis. Renly is popular at court because of his friendly manner and keen fashion
        sense. \n\n Renly has been involved in a homosexual romance with Ser Loras Tyrell for many
        years. They must keep their love a secret because the dominant religion of the realm, the
        Faith of the Seven, considers homosexuality to be a sin, although many people are
        nonetheless aware of their relationship as something of an open secret.</string>

    <!-- Character Selyse Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_selyse">Selyse Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_selyse">Selyse is the wife of Stannis Baratheon,
        the Lord of Dragonstone and claimant to the Iron Throne. She was born into House Florent
        of Brightwater Keep, a noble house of the Reach and bannermen of House Tyrell. \n\n Selyse
        and Stannis have a single daughter, Princess Shireen Baratheon. The rest of Selyse and
        Stannis&#8217; offspring, Petyr, Tommard, and Edric, were all stillborn. She keeps their bodies
        in crystal containers filled with chemicals in her chambers.</string>

    <!-- Character Shireen Baratheon -->
    <string name="title_character_baratheon_shireen">Shireen Baratheon</string>
    <string name="background_character_baratheon_shireen">Shireen is the daughter of Stannis and
        Selyse Baratheon. Her father is the head of House Baratheon of Dragonstone and has declared
        himself King on the Iron Throne. Shireen is Stannis&#8217;s only living child and therefore his
        heir presumptive. She is the same age as Arya Stark. She had three older brothers, who were
        stillborn. \n\n The left side of her face is scarred by Greyscale, which she caught as an
        infant. Normally considered a death sentence, Stannis refused to give up on her and called
        in every healer he could find from both sides of the Narrow Sea to try to cure her, and
        through the combination of their efforts they managed to succeed, though the left side of
        her face was left permanently scarred. \n\n Selyse resents Shireen because she could not
        give Stannis a healthy son, only a sickly daughter, and dismisses her as stubborn and
        sinful. Shireen in turn tries to avoid her mother, because she is frightened by Selyse&#8217;s
        fanatical devotion to Melisandre and the Lord of Light. However, Shireen adores her father
        and he loves her deeply as well, though he is a dour man who doesn&#8217;t often let it show
        through his stern exterior. She is also close friends with Stannis&#8217;s most trusted advisor,
        Ser Davos Seaworth.</string>

    <!-- Character Brienne of Tarth -->
    <string name="title_character_tarth_brienne">Brienne of Tarth</string>
    <string name="background_character_tarth_brienne">Brienne is the sole surviving child and heir
        of Lord Selwyn Tarth of Evenfall Hall, on the island of Tarth, located in the Narrow Sea
        off the coast of the Stormlands. She is unusually tall and muscular for a woman by
        Westerosi standards and developed a taste for martial activity as a child. Brienne has
        grown up to become skilled at arms and dreams of becoming a knight. \n\n Brienne&#8217;s mother
        died when she was so young that she doesn&#8217;t remember her. She had some siblings but they all
        died in childhood. As the sole heir of House Tarth, she posed a fairly promising marriage
        prospect for men from other noble Houses, but due to her physicality and personality has
        never seriously pursued a marriage alliance with another House. \n\n She is also called The
        Maid of Tarth, or, disparagingly, Brienne the Beauty, due to her appearance.</string>

    <!-- Character Gendry -->
    <string name="title_character_gendry">Gendry</string>
    <string name="background_character_gendry">Gendry is a bastard son of King Robert Baratheon,
        but is unacknowledged and unaware of his lineage. Gendry did not receive the bastard
        surname used in the Crownlands (Waters) because he was not openly acknowledged by Robert.
        \n\n His mother worked in a tavern and died when he was very young. When he was old enough,
        an unknown lord paid his apprentice fee so he could learn to be a blacksmith. He spent his
        whole life in the capital city of King&#8217;s Landing working as an apprentice blacksmith under
        his master, Tobho Mott, to forge armor and weapons for the nobility.</string>


    <!-- Character Davos Seaworth -->
    <string name="title_character_seaworth_davos">Davos Seaworth</string>
    <string name="background_character_seaworth_davos">Ser Davos Seaworth is a landed knight and a
        reformed smuggler. His ship used to ply the Narrow Sea, smuggling goods from the Free
        Cities into the Seven Kingdoms and back again. \n\n Davos was born in Flea Bottom, the
        poorest slum in King&#8217;s Landing. His father was a poor crabber. He became a sailor while
        very young to escape the slums and has spent most of his life sailing the Narrow Sea. His
        black-sailed ship became infamous for sneaking into harbors in the dead of night while
        avoiding detection. \n\n During Robert&#8217;s Rebellion, Davos aided Stannis Baratheon while he
        was besieged in Storm&#8217;s End, by delivering smuggled onions and other foodstuffs into the
        castle. The supplies helped Stannis&#8217; forces survive until the end of the war. For this
        service, Stannis rewarded Davos by bestowing him with knighthood and lands. He chose the
        name &#8220;Seaworth&#8221; for his family&#8217;s new noble House, as a reference to his smuggling past.
        Highborn members of older noble Houses disparagingly called Davos &#8220;the Onion Knight&#8221; for
        his actions, but he has embraced this title and proudly took an onion for a sigil and sewed
        it onto his ship&#8217;s sails. \n\n Stannis also cut off four finger tips from Davos&#8217; right hand
        as punishment for his smuggling crimes. Thieves in Westeros are often sentenced to having
        fingers or the whole hand removed, but Stannis only took the fingertips of his less used
        hand (his right, as Davos is left-handed). Davos submitted to this punishment willingly,
        judging it a fair exchange in return for improving his family&#8217;s future prospects. He also
        mentions in a featurette that he submitted to the punishment for the sake of sheer justice,
        saying he &#8220;avoided punishment for too long&#8221;. He wears his severed finger bones in a pouch
        about his neck and believes they bring him good luck. \n\n Davos is one of Stannis&#8217; most
        loyal and reliable vassals and arguably his best friend, but is treated with disdain by
        some of the other lords of Westeros for his low birth. Stannis himself points out that it
        was the low-born Davos, and not the high-born lords, who saved the lives of Stannis and his
        castle garrison. Davos is one of the only men who can (even grudgingly) influence Stannis&#8217;
        decisions, because he values Davos&#8217; honest advice above that of noble-born flatterers. \n\n
        Davos has several sons, including Matthos, who serves with him on his ship and is a scribe
        for Stannis. He is proud of his son&#8217;s education but remains illiterate. \n\n Even though
        Stannis&#8217; wife Selyse despises Ser Davos, their daughter Shireen is fond of him and
        considers him a friend.</string>

    <!-- Character Salladhor Saan -->
    <string name="title_character_saan_salladhor">Salladhor Saan</string>
    <string name="background_character_saan_salladhor">Salladhor Saan is a pirate-lord from Lys,
        though a native of the Summer Isles. He commands a fleet of thirty ships that frequently
        prey on merchant ships traveling between Westeros and the Free Cities to the east.
        Sometimes in pursuit of extra wealth, he shifts from pure piracy to being a sellsail:
        hiring out the services of his ships and crews to the highest bidder, to act as mercenaries
        in various conflicts.</string>

    <!-- Character Melisandre -->
    <string name="title_character_melisandre">Melisandre</string>
    <string name="background_character_melisandre">Originally born a slave in Essos, Melisandre is
        a Red Priestess of the Lord of Light, a deity that is not widely worshiped in Westeros.
        Hailing from Asshai, a country located in the far east of the continent of Essos, she
        claims to wield powerful magical abilities, particularly the power of prophecy. Melisandre
        wears a large ruby necklace that seems to glow whenever she performs her magic. Some years
        ago she crossed the Narrow Sea and came to the court of Lord Stannis Baratheon on the
        island stronghold of Dragonstone, to preach her faith. Stannis and the majority of his
        household have now converted to her religion, and she has become a close adviser to Stannis
        himself.</string>

    <!-- Character Daenerys Targaryen -->
    <string name="title_character_targaryen_daenerys">Daenerys Targaryen</string>
    <string name="background_character_targaryen_daenerys">Daenerys is the only daughter and
        youngest child of King Aerys II Targaryen, the &#8220;Mad King&#8221;, and his sister-wife Rhaella.
        Her father died during the Sack of King&#8217;s Landing, before she was even born. The usurper
        Robert Baratheon installed himself as king, having defeated Aerys in the conquest known as
        Robert&#8217;s Rebellion. Her pregnant mother and young brother Viserys, fled to the island of
        Dragonstone, the ancestral home of House Targaryen, to escape Robert. Daenerys&#8217;s brother
        Rhaegar Targaryen was also killed in the war and Robert&#8217;s forces murdered his wife and
        children, Daenerys&#8217;s sister-in-law, niece, and nephew, during the Sack of King&#8217;s Landing. \n\n
        On the night Daenerys was born on Dragonstone, a vast storm raged. For this reason, she is
        sometimes called &#8220;Daenerys Stormborn&#8221;. Her mother died soon after she was born, leaving her
        an orphan. As a baby, she was taken into exile in the Free Cities with her brother,
        Viserys, by loyal retainers, among them Ser Willem Darry.\n\n After years spent fruitlessly
        trying to raise support to retake the Iron Throne, Viserys and Daenerys were given
        sanctuary by Magister Illyrio Mopatis in the Free City of Pentos. She dreams of finding a
        peaceful home and a place to belong. She lives in constant fear of Viserys, who hits her
        when his temper is risen (in his words, whenever she &#8220;wakes the dragon&#8221;). Living under
        Viserys&#8217; domination has left her meek and malleable.</string>

    <!-- Character Viserys Targaryen -->
    <string name="title_character_targaryen_viserys">Viserys Targaryen</string>
    <string name="background_character_targaryen_viserys">Viserys is the second son and heir of
        King Aerys II Targaryen, the former ruler of the Seven Kingdoms. During Robert&#8217;s Rebellion,
        after Viserys&#8217;s older brother Rhaegar was killed at the Battle of the Trident, his father
        sent Viserys and his pregnant mother Queen Rhaella to safety on Dragonstone island. King
        Aerys was soon afterwards killed during the Sack of King&#8217;s Landing along with Rhaegar&#8217;s
        widow and children, and thus at the age of only five Viserys became the titular head of
        House Targaryen, though by this point the war was officially lost. Not long afterwards,
        his mother died in childbirth, while the forces of Robert Baratheon closed in on the
        island. Before they could arrive, Viserys and his baby sister Daenerys were smuggled to
        safety in the Free Cities, across the Narrow Sea on the continent of Essos. Bereft of
        followers, Viserys spent the next 17 years travelling between the Free Cities trying to
        find new supporters for an attempt to retake the Iron Throne. At times, however, he was
        left literally begging for food and shelter, much less an army. \n\n Viserys claims the
        title of Lord of the Seven Kingdoms and refers to Robert Baratheon only as &#8220;the Usurper&#8221;.
        After years spent fruitlessly wandering the Free Cities seeking military support to retake
        his throne, Viserys and Daenerys became guests of the powerful Magister Illyrio Mopatis of
        Pentos.</string>

    <!-- Character Aerys II Targaryen -->
    <string name="title_character_targaryen_aerys">Aerys II Targaryen</string>
    <string name="background_character_targaryen_aerys">Aerys Targaryen, the Second of His Name,
        was King of the Seven Kingdoms and the last member of House Targaryen to sit on the Iron
        Throne. Popularly remembered as &#8220;the Mad King&#8221;, his reign became increasingly erratic and
        murderous. A final round of blood-letting, unleashed when his son, Prince Rhaegar,
        kidnapped Lyanna Stark of Winterfell, saw many houses in the realm rebel against his rule.
        Brandon Stark protested the abduction of his sister and demanded justice. Aerys had him
        arrested for treason and then offered to ransom him to his father. When Rickard Stark rode
        to King&#8217;s Landing to ransom Brandon, Aerys had him arrested too, and then brutally executed
        both father and son. \n\n The noble houses of Stark, Tully, Arryn, and Baratheon raised the
        flags of rebellion and destroyed the royalist armies in several major engagements,
        culminating in the Battle of the Trident where Prince Rhaegar fell. King Aerys was betrayed
        by his former friend and King&#8217;s Hand, Lord Tywin Lannister, who led an army to apparently
        defend the capital at King&#8217;s Landing but instead brutally sacked the city. \n\n Aerys had
        already instructed Wisdom Rossart, his new Hand of the King, to hide caches of wildfire all
        over King&#8217;s Landing. He then decreed that the capital be set ablaze. Aerys seemingly
        believed the massive inferno would transmute him into a dragon and he would emerge to
        obliterate his enemies. To prevent the King incinerating the city and its half a million
        inhabitants, Ser Jaime Lannister, a member of the Kingsguard, stabbed Aerys in the back and
        then cut his throat. \n\n Aerys&#8217; death brought to an end the Targaryen dynasty, which had
        ruled the Seven Kingdoms for three centuries. He was replaced on the Iron Throne by the
        leader of the rebels, Robert Baratheon. However, the Targaryen bloodline survived through
        his two youngest children, Viserys and Daenerys, who were spirited away to the Free
        Cities.</string>

    <!-- Character Rhaegar Targaryen -->
    <string name="title_character_targaryen_rhaegar">Rhaegar Targaryen</string>
    <string name="background_character_targaryen_rhaegar">Prince Rhaegar Targaryen was the eldest
        son and heir to the Mad King, Aerys II Targaryen, by his wife and sister Queen Rhaella
        Targaryen. Tywin Lannister desired for his daughter Cersei to marry Rhaegar, but King
        Aerys II insulted Tywin by indicating that such a match would be beneath Rhaegar. Instead,
        Rhaegar was married to Princess Elia Martell of Dorne, with whom he had a daughter named
        Rhaenys and then a son named Aegon. In spite of Elia&#8217;s love and loyalty to him, Rhaegar
        abducted Lyanna Stark of Winterfell for unknown reasons. \n\n After the Mad King had Lyanna
        Stark&#8217;s father Rickard Stark and oldest brother Brandon Stark executed after the latter
        brazenly rode to the capital, demanding Rhaegar release Lyanna, her other brother, Eddard
        Stark, and her betrothed, Robert Baratheon, joined forces with several other houses to
        overthrow the Targaryen dynasty. This war became known as the War of the Usurper or
        Robert&#8217;s Rebellion. After initially remaining away from the fighting in Dorne, Rhaegar was
        summoned to lead the Royalist forces in what would be the Battle of the Trident. During the
        Battle, Rhaegar was killed in single combat with Lyanna&#8217;s betrothed Robert Baratheon.
        Rhaegar was struck down with a massive blow from Robert&#8217;s warhammer, which scattered the
        rubies encrusted in Rhaegar&#8217;s armor under the water. That location was named the &#8220;Ruby
        Ford&#8221; thereafter. \n\n His father was killed shortly afterwards by Ser Jaime Lannister
        during the Sack of King&#8217;s Landing and his mother died in childbirth at Dragonstone. His
        younger brother Viserys and sister Daenerys (who was born after Rhaegar&#8217;s death) survived
        in exile in the Free Cities across the sea. Lyanna also died during the war. Rhaenys and
        Aegon were killed in front of Elia by Ser Gregor Clegane better known as &#8217;The Mountain&#8217;
        and afterwards raped Elia and fatally stabbed her with his sword.</string>

    <!-- Character Aemon Targaryen -->
    <string name="title_character_targaryen_aemon">Aemon Targaryen</string>
    <string name="background_character_targaryen_aemon">Aemon was born into the royal House
        Targaryen, the son of King Maekar I. Unlike the majority of his forbears, Aemon and his
        brothers were not born out of marriage between brother and sister. Their father and
        grandfather respectively married Dyanna of House Dayne and Myriah of House Martell.
        Originally known as Prince Aemon Targaryen, he was not his father&#8217;s eldest son, so he
        eventually joined the order of Maesters. Aemon gave up all rights to inheritance when he
        took his vows, which also included dropping his surname &#8220;Targaryen&#8221;. \n\n Aemon&#8217;s older
        brother, Aerion, later died, however, and despite being a sworn maester there were those
        who felt that the crown should pass to him. Aemon refused the throne, however, and it
        passed to his younger brother, who became King Aegon V. Aemon then joined the Night&#8217;s Watch
        to remove himself from the political intrigues of the royal court, and those who wished to
        set him up as a rival against his brother. \n\n Many years later the crown passed to Aegon
        V&#8217;s son, Aemon&#8217;s nephew Aerys II, called &#8220;The Mad King&#8221;. Aerys&#8217;s growing insanity
        ultimately led to the outbreak of Robert&#8217;s Rebellion, which saw House Targaryen deposed
        and practically exterminated. Upon hearing about the brutal death of his family in King&#8217;s
        Landing during the rebellion, Aemon bore great sadness which has never left him. \n\n
        Around one hundred years old, Aemon is thought to be one of the oldest living men in
        Westeros, though he has retained all of his wits and his mind is still very sharp. He has
        served as the maester at Castle Black for many decades. \n\n Aemon has long since gone
        blind due to old age. It is not clear when he went blind (he was not born blind), though
        he has stated that he was already old and blind during Robert&#8217;s Rebellion. As a man of
        learning, he laments not being able to read anymore, even though Castle Black ironically
        has an ancient and well-stocked library consisting of thousands of books. Because one of a
        maester&#8217;s basic duties is to handle messages sent to and from a castle by messenger-ravens,
        Aemon has to rely on the assistance of others to physically read the letters for
        him.</string>

    <!-- Character Drogo -->
    <string name="title_character_drogo">Drogo</string>
    <string name="background_character_drogo">Drogo is a khal or warlord of the Dothraki, the
        famed nomadic horse-lords of the eastern continent beyond the Narrow Sea. The Dothraki are
        fierce warriors, skilled in battle, unrelenting in combat and known for savagery towards
        non-Dothraki. Amongst their own people they have a code of honor, albeit still a harsh and
        unforgiving one. Drogo was very young to have his own khalasar, particularly such a large
        one. He is a legendary warrior and has never been defeated in battle. Drogo desired the
        most beautiful and exotic woman in the world as his khaleesi or wife, and enlisted Magister
        Illyrio Mopatis of Pentos to help him find such a woman. \n\n He is guarded by bloodriders
        including Qotho. Generals or ko in his khalasar include Pono and Jhaqo, men who guard him,
        follow him in battle and, when Drogo dies, it is their duty and honor to follow him even
        then to continue serving him.</string>

    <!-- Character Missandei -->
    <string name="title_character_missandei">Missandei</string>
    <string name="background_character_missandei">Missandei was born on the island of Naath in the
        Summer Sea, off the coast of the continent of Sothoryos. She was enslaved at a young age
        and taken to Slaver&#8217;s Bay in Essos, where she was eventually put to work as an interpreter
        for the slaver-master Kraznys mo Nakloz, one of the Good Masters of Astapor. \n\n Missandei
        speaks nineteen languages including High Valyrian (her favorite), the Low Valyrian dialect
        of Slaver&#8217;s Bay, Dothraki, the Common Tongue of Westeros, and has some knowledge of the
        functionally dead language of the Ghiscari Empire.</string>

    <!-- Character Grey Worm -->
    <string name="title_character_worm_grey">Grey Worm</string>
    <string name="background_character_worm_grey">Grey Worm was originally a boy taken into slavery
        by the Good Masters of Astapor, an oligarchy of slave-traders dedicated to the training and
        commerce of Unsullied, warrior-eunuch slaves trained into absolute obedience since early
        childhood. It later is revealed that he is originally from the Summer Islands and was taken
        by the slavers in a raid as a baby. He has no memory of his life before being an Unsullied.
        \n\n He is released from slavery after Daenerys Targaryen buys all the Unsullied in the
        city and has them put all slave owners in Astapor to the sword and release all slaves.
        Once released, Grey Worm, like all his brethren, chooses to fight for Daenerys as a free
        man.</string>

    <!-- Character Daario Naharis -->
    <string name="title_character_naharis_daario">Daario Naharis</string>
    <string name="background_character_naharis_daario">Daario is a Tyroshi sellsword, employed as a
        lieutenant in the Second Sons. He is apparently held in high enough regard by the company&#8217;s
        co-captains, Mero and Prendahl na Ghezn, that they allow him to join them in contract
        negotiations and discussions of the company&#8217;s future. \n\n According to Daario, his mother
        was a prostitute, and he comes from low beginnings. At the age of 12, Daario was sold by
        his mother to a slave master from Tolos due to her declining income, alcoholism and his
        aggressive, unruly behavior and tendency to get into fights with other boys. He was trained
        as a pit fighter and had his first match in the pits when he was 16. Daario rose to fame
        within the fighting pits earning his master so much money that at the time of his master&#8217;s
        death Daario was rewarded with freedom. Daario chose to fight as a sellsword for the Second
        Sons sometime after that. \n\n Besides being fluent in the Common Tongue, Daario is also
        fluent in High Valyrian considering he is of Tyroshi origin. \n\n Daario has an unusual
        code for a sellsword; he won&#8217;t sleep with prostitutes and only kills soldiers who are
        trying to kill him, not bystanders. He does this because he feels that otherwise there is
        no sport and it is not exciting. Daario has said that the gods gave men two things to
        entertain themselves with before they die: the thrill of having sex with a woman who
        earnestly wants it, and the thrill of killing a man who is trying to kill you first. \n\n
        Daario is a highly skilled and extremely capable warrior. Being trained a pit fighter since
        the age of 12 and then fighting as a sellsword after that, mostly all of Daario&#8217;s life has
        revolved around fighting. During his years as a pit fighter he learned to fight with
        several different fighting styles; like a Dothraki screamer, a Norvoshi priest and a
        Westerosi knight. Daario has over several different occasions proven his skills in combat:
        when he reveals to Daenerys that he single-handedly managed to kill both of the commanding
        officers of the Second Sons, when he along Ser Jorah and Grey Worm fight severely
        outnumbered against several guards in the streets of Yunkai, when he kills the Champion of
        Meereen in single combat with ease or when protecting Daenerys, Tyrion, and Missandei from
        hundreds of Sons of the Harpy along with Ser Jorah, coming out on top, unharmed, despite
        being outnumbered severely. \n\n Daario&#8217;s weapons-of-choice are a Dothraki arakh and a
        Myrish stiletto, both which have gold-plated custom-made hilts in the shape of beautiful,
        naked women. His fighting style is based on speed and quick, accurate strikes with few,
        mostly finishing, blows based on pure strength due to his relatively small size and lean
        build compared to the larger, stronger opponents he frequently faced in the fighting
        pits.</string>

    <!-- Character Doran Martell -->
    <string name="title_character_martell_doran">Doran Martell</string>
    <string name="background_character_martell_doran">Doran Martell is the Prince of Dorne and the
        Lord of Sunspear. He is the head of House Martell, the ruling house of Dorne, and the older
        brother of the late Princess Elia, who was murdered by Ser Gregor Clegane in the Sack of
        King&#8217;s Landing, and Prince Oberyn, known as The Red Viper, also killed by Clegane. \n\n He
        suffers from a severe case of gout, which mostly prevents him from walking and restricts
        him to a wheelchair. \n\n Unlike his more hotheaded and aggressive brother, Oberyn, Doran
        is a pensive, calculating, and patient man who always waits and observes before making his
        next move. Despite their different personalities, the two brothers were very close. While
        Oberyn could indulge in the wayward Dornish ways, challenging whomever he liked regardless
        of the consequences, Doran was raised to be more responsible as the heir to the Dornish
        throne. He truly cares for both his people and his family, and would never make a decision
        that would go against their interests. However, this is often against their wishes. \n\n
        Doran has also been a witness to war and was deeply marked by its consequences. As such,
        he often tries to find a solution that avoids waging war, even if the honor of House
        Martell has been offended. This, along with his physical weakness, gives some people the
        impression that he is weak-willed and can be easily dominated, but this is misleading;
        Doran is just as ruthless and decisive as any other member of House Martell. He&#8217;s simply
        better at hiding it - until the moment that he strikes.</string>

    <!-- Character Trystane Martell -->
    <string name="title_character_martell_trystane">Trystane Martell</string>
    <string name="background_character_martell_trystane">Prince Trystane is a member of House
        Martell, the ruling house of Dorne. He is the youngest son of Prince Doran Martell, Lord
        of Sunspear and Prince of Dorne. Like his father Doran, Trystane lacks (for the most part)
        the hotheadedness typical of Dornishmen, as evidenced by his showing mercy to Bronn for
        attacking him.</string>

    <!-- Character Elia Martell -->
    <string name="title_character_martell_elia">Elia Martell</string>
    <string name="background_character_martell_elia">Princess Elia was the wife of Prince Rhaegar
        Targaryen. They had two children; a daughter Rhaenys, and a son, Aegon. She was born into
        House Martell in Dorne. She was the younger sister of Prince Doran Martell, the current
        ruler of Dorne, and an older sister of Prince Oberyn. Her marriage to Prince Rhaegar
        was arranged by King Aerys II Targaryen and considered an insult by Tywin Lannister,
        Aerys&#8217;s Hand of the King, who had proposed his daughter Cersei as a bride for the Prince
        but was rejected. The marriage was one of the reasons Lord Tywin resigned his post as
        Hand. Like her younger brother, Elia was very popular among the Dornish people. \n\n As a
        teenager, Elia accompanied her brother Oberyn on a visit to Casterly Rock. While there,
        Elia and Oberyn were eager to see the monster that had just been born. Cersei finally
        showed them the baby, but the Martell siblings were somewhat disappointed to see that
        Tyrion was just a baby, and somewhat disturbed by Cersei&#8217;s already strong hatred of him.
        \n\n Elia loved her husband Prince Rhaegar dearly. She bore him two children, Rhaenys and
        Aegon, to whom she was equally devoted; according to Oberyn, Elia took care of them from
        birth, rather than delegating the task to a wet nurse. Both pregnancies were very
        difficult, and each nearly killed Elia. \n\n When Robert&#8217;s Rebellion erupted, Elia was
        kept in King&#8217;s Landing by King Aerys to ensure the loyalty of House Martell during the
        conflict- a measure the Martells considered unnecessary, as they would always fight for
        whichever side Elia was on and had no intention of breaking their oaths of loyalty to the
        Targaryens. Ultimately Rhaegar was killed in personal combat with Robert Baratheon at the
        Battle of the Trident, leaving Elia widowed. A few weeks later during the Sack of King&#8217;s
        Landing, Tywin Lannister&#8217;s army betrayed the Targaryens and overran the city. Ser Gregor
        Clegane - known as &#8220;The Mountain That Rides&#8221; burst into the royal chambers and before
        Elia&#8217;s eyes, killed her daughter Rhaenys, then bashed her infant son&#8217;s head in against a
        wall. Covered in the blood and gore of her children, Gregor proceeded to brutally rape
        Elia, and finally he killed her. It is rumored that he cut her in half with his
        greatsword, though Gregor himself later confesses to &#8220;smashing her head in&#8221;. \n\n Elia&#8217;s
        death deeply alienated her family from the crown after Robert ascended the throne, and
        their hatred of the Lannisters now knew no bounds. Subsequently they were never seen and
        rarely if ever mentioned at the royal court in King&#8217;s Landing.</string>

    <!-- Character Oberyn Martell -->
    <string name="title_character_martell_oberyn">Oberyn Martell</string>
    <string name="background_character_martell_oberyn">Prince Oberyn is the younger brother of
        Prince Doran Martell and Princess Elia Martell; like most members of House Martell, he is
        styled &#8220;Prince&#8221; instead of &#8220;Lord&#8221;. He is nicknamed &#8220;the Red Viper&#8221; for his knowledge of
        poisons and for his unusual, deadly style of combat. Oberyn is known for being an
        accomplished warrior, but he is just as infamous for his sexual appetite, which extends to
        both men and women; Tyrion Lannister tells Bronn that Oberyn is &#8220;famous for fucking half of
        Westeros&#8221;. Oberyn&#8217;s paramour is Ellaria Sand; she is his wife in all but name, and Doran
        once noted that Ellaria made Oberyn very happy. She is also the mother of five of Oberyn&#8217;s
        infamous eight bastard daughters, all of whom he has acknowledged and given his love and
        care. He named the fifth one, Elia Sand, after his late sister. \n\n When he was a teenager,
        Oberyn was accompianed by his big sister Elia on a visit to Casterly Rock. While there,
        Oberyn and Elia were eager to see the &#8220;monster&#8221; that had just been born. Cersei finally
        showed them Tyrion, but the Martell siblings were somewhat disappointed to see that he was
        just a baby, and somewhat disturbed by Cersei&#8217;s already strong hatred of him. \n\n Prince
        Oberyn trained at the Citadel in his youth, in order to become a maester. Although he
        ultimately grew bored and abandoned his studies, he managed to forge several links in a
        maester&#8217;s chain, and became well versed in the use of poisons in the process. When he was
        sixteen, an older nobleman caught Oberyn in bed with his mistress and challenged Oberyn to
        a duel to first blood; Oberyn won the duel, and several days later the man died from
        festering wounds, likely because Oberyn had poisoned his blade. Oberyn also travelled to
        Essos in his youth; for a time, he served in the mercenary company known as the Second Sons.
        He once went to the city of Astapor there and saw the Unsullied, whom he jokingly remarked
        were impressive on the battlefield, but less so in the bedroom. He lived in Essos for a
        total of five years. It is implied that Oberyn fought duels in the infamous fighting pits
        of Meereen, as he mentions to Tyrion that he learned some of his combat techniques
        &#8220;during his years in the fighting pits&#8221;. \n\n Despite his wayward ways and liberal attitude
        towards sexuality, Oberyn is very devoted to his family, telling his lover Ellaria that any
        other person would always have to wait behind her for his affection. He was very close with
        his sister, Elia, and took her death very hard. As a result, he had a strong and fierce
        hatred for House Lannister, especially towards Tywin Lannister, whom he believed ordered
        his sister&#8217;s murder. He was also close to his older brother, Doran, despite their very
        different personalities.</string>

    <!-- Character Ellaria Sand -->
    <string name="title_character_sand_ellaria">Ellaria Sand</string>
    <string name="background_character_sand_ellaria">Ellaria is the mother of four of Prince
        Oberyn Martell&#8217;s eight bastard daughters. Her eldest daughter is Tyene. Like Oberyn,
        Ellaria is attracted to both men and women.</string>

    <!-- Character Obara Sand -->
    <string name="title_character_sand_obara">Obara Sand</string>
    <string name="background_character_sand_obara">Obara Sand is the eldest of the &#8220;Sand Snakes&#8221;,
        the eight bastard daughters of Prince Oberyn Martell, and was named in honor of her father.
        Her mother was a peasant. \n\n Even more than her sisters, Obara inherited her father&#8217;s
        martial prowess, particularly his skill with a spear. She is a very tough warrior and the
        most overtly martial of the Sand Snakes. The other Sand Snakes will change out of their
        light leather armor when traveling in the hot deserts of Dorne, but Obara always wears her
        leather armor. She also tends to dress in a more masculine style than her sisters, even
        when not in combat. When she sees an obstacle, she does not attempt to undermine it with
        deception or intrigue, but will attack it head-on, relying on her skill and the strength of
        her weapons. This is in contrast with her sister Nymeria, who prefers to hold off and
        analyze her foes to calculate a more efficient means of defeating them. \n\n Obara is the
        Sand Snake most like their father. He taught her the ways of war himself, training her in
        the use of a traditional Dornish spear like he used. Unlike most Dornishmen, who are
        overtly passionate, Obara is staunchly disciplined to not overtly display her emotions.
        This is largely due to her origins: unlike her sisters Nymeria and Tyene, Obara&#8217;s mother
        was not a noblewoman, so when Oberyn came to take her to court, she had to choose between
        staying or going, the latter meaning she would never see her mother again. As a result, she
        has a cold and hardened demeanor, though she deeply loves her family. This is not to say
        that Obara is the most rational of the sisters (Nymeria is the most rational and
        calculating one). She is actually quite irrational and ruled by her emotions, she just
        doesn&#8217;t outwardly show them that much. The difference is that in a situation where Tyene
        would aggressively shout insults at an enemy and attack them, Obara would just silently
        walk straight up to them and stab them without saying a word. Nymeria, in contrast, would
        hold back and attempt to assess if there would be a more opportune moment to strike at a
        later time. \n\n Obara is loosely the lead Sand Snake, because she is eldest and probably
        the best fighter. Her sister Nymeria does nothing without her approval. Her father Oberyn
        and Nymeria were the only two people that Obara ever fully trusted. As her close confident,
        Nymeria is also the only person who can say &#8220;no&#8221; to Obara: while they may seem to argue at
        times, conversely this is because Nymeria is the only person that Obara will at least pay
        heed to - for anyone else, arguing with Obara is useless once she has her mind set on
        something. Nymeria is the only person Obara will ever take advice from (after their
        father&#8217;s death).</string>

    <!-- Character Nymeria Sand -->
    <string name="title_character_sand_nymeria">Nymeria Sand</string>
    <string name="background_character_sand_nymeria">Nymeria Sand is the second of the eight
        bastard daughters of Prince Oberyn Martell, known as the &#8220;Sand Snakes&#8221;. Nymeria&#8217;s mother
        was an Eastern noblewoman, who taught her how to use a whip in combat, but who later died
        in battle. Nymeria became very skilled with using her 8 foot long bullwhip in combat. \n\n
        Nymeria inherited her father&#8217;s cunning, and is the most observant and calculating of the
        Sand Snakes. Instead of charging head-on into a situation relying on brute strength (like
        her older sister Obara), she will stand back and observe her enemy&#8217;s weak points, then move
        in precisely for an accurate strike. In this, she is actually more like her uncle, Doran
        Martell, than like her father. Her choice of a bullwhip as her primary weapon exemplifies
        this mentality. She hones her reflexes by playing a sparring game with her younger sister
        Tyene, in which one slaps the other&#8217;s hands before they can move them; Nymeria claims she
        has never lost this game.\n\n Nymeria dresses more femininely than her martial sister Obara,
        though she is no less deadly. Nymeria has long flowing hair, and alluring Dornish-style
        dresses. \n\n She is named after Nymeria, the warrior-queen of the Rhoynar who led her
        people&#8217;s migration to Dorne one thousand years ago. The original Nymeria unified Dorne for
        the first time, and is considered the founder of House Martell in its modern form.
        &#8220;Nymeria&#8221; is a popular name in Dorne, much as &#8220;Brandon&#8221; is in the North, after their
        founder Brandon the Builder. Through her father Oberyn, Nymeria Sand is actually a direct
        descendant of the original Nymeria.</string>

    <!-- Character Tyene Sand -->
    <string name="title_character_sand_tyene">Tyene Sand</string>
    <string name="background_character_sand_tyene">Tyene Sand is the third of the eight bastard
        daughters of Prince Oberyn Martell, known as the &#8220;Sand Snakes&#8221;. She is also his eldest
        daughter by his paramour, Ellaria Sand. Tyene fights using a pair of long daggers, though
        her other signature weapon is her skill with poisons - a tactic she learned from her
        father. Like her father, she is known to coat her blades with poisons, making a single
        scratch lethal. \n\n Tyene can feign being soft-spoken and childlike, but this is just an
        act to keep her enemies off guard, as she is just as fierce as her older sisters. \n\n Tyene
        is the youngest of the four adult Sand Snakes, and more impetuous than her older sisters
        Obara and Nymeria. Where Obara will face threats head-on (confident in her martial prowess),
        and Nymeria will stand back and analyze the situation to make a precise strike at her
        enemy&#8217;s weak points, Tyene tends to heedlessly charge ahead. This is exemplified by her
        choice of daggers as her main hand-held weapon: they are quick on the draw, allowing her
        to lash out quickly, before even her older sisters can restrain her.</string>

    <!-- Character Areo Hotah -->
    <string name="title_character_hotah_areo">Areo Hotah</string>
    <string name="background_character_hotah_areo">Areo Hotah is originally from Norvos, one of
        the northern Free Cities. He joined the Martell household at Sunspear along with Prince
        Doran&#8217;s wife, a Norvoshi noblewoman. He has been a trusted servant of the Martells for
        many years, and is renowned for his skill with his halberd. Hotah&#8217;s motto is &#8220;Serve,
        Protect, Obey&#8221;.</string>

</resources>
